<deck><topics><topic type=""><title>Funky Fungus</title><description>Funky Fungus is a Bunny Modifier that a player would most likely place under an opponent’s bunny in The Bunny Circle. The opponent cannot refuse a Funky Fungus Bunny Modifier. Funky Fungus raises the level of any weapon played on the bunny by the amount of Funky Fungus illustrated on the card. For example, if a bunny has the Funky Fungus Double Bunny Modifier, then a level 6 weapon placed on the bunny would become a level 8 weapon.</description></topic><topic type="gameplay"><title>Morden’s Metals Exchange Starter Card</title><description>At the start of the game, the three 6-sided dice (Gold, Silver and Copper) are rolled. The numbers rolled set the Exchange Rate for the three metals. These three dice are not included in this Booster Deck, but any three 6-sided dice may be used.

A player may exchange (buy or sell) Metal cards or coins anytime during his turn from Morden’s Metals Exchange for Kaballa Dolla. Kaballa Dolla is taken from the Discard Pile by any player exchanging Metal cards or coins. Dolla Vouchers (Ominous Onyx Booster Deck) are taken from any Kaballa’s Market if no Kaballa Dolla exist in the Discard Pile.

All Metal cards or coins sold to Morden’s Metals Exchange are kept face up next to the Morden’s Metals Exchange Starter Card. Players may only buy the Metal cards or coins that are available at Morden’s Metals Exchange.

All Metal dice may be re-rolled by a player at the end of any of his turns during which he received a Carrot. Carrots are considered received if the player bought the Carrot from any Kaballa’s Market or used a card (such as Choose A Carrot) to acquire it. Trading Carrots with other players does not give a player the privilege to re-roll the Metal dice.

A player may not exchange Metal cards or coins during the same turn once he has rolled the Metal dice. The new Exchange Rate will be available starting with the next player.

Cards exist that double the value of certain metals at Morden’s Metals Exchange. If played, place the doubling card on top of the Morden’s Metals Exchange Starter Card. More than one doubling card may be used at the same time to modify the Exchange Rate.</description></topic><topic type="gameplay"><title>Roaming Red Run Cards</title><description>Any card that has a Red RUN printed in the top window is a Roaming Red Run card. Roaming Red Run cards are played differently than regular Run cards because they may remain in play for many rounds.

For example, suppose that a fictional player named Carol launches Where The Buffalo Roam. Naturally she would place it on an opponent, and that opponent would have to feed the buffalo 5 units of any food (Cabbage, Water, Radish or Milk – in any combination) or lose a Carrot (return it to any Kaballa’s Market). After the first play however, Where The Buffalo Roam is not discarded. Instead, it is given to the next adjacent player counter-clockwise in The Bunny Circle. Where The Buffalo Roam remains with the next player and collects its food at the end of Carol’s turn (one round of play later). Where The Buffalo Roam will move from player to player and continue to feed once per round of play always at the end of Carol’s turn. It is possible that Where The Buffalo Roam may, eventually, be given to Carol and she will have to feed the buffalo!

This cycle continues until the Roaming Red Run card is eliminated (the buffalo encounters a player with no food, or it is attacked and eliminated by any weapon).</description></topic><topic type="gameplay"><title>Senators</title><description>When a player draws a Senator Bunny Modifier card from the Draw Pile he must immediately place it under any bunny in The Bunny Circle. Most likely a player will want to assign that Senator card to one of his own bunnies. If a player draws a Senator card and has no bunnies of his own, then he must place the Senator card under an opponent’s bunny. If there are no bunnies in The Bunny Circle, then the Senator card is discarded.

If a player is given a Senator card during the initial deal at the start of the game, then he must discard it. Another card should be chosen from the Draw Pile.

Creative Team Alpha would like to go on record as saying that the Whiner party is not in any way related to alcoholic beverages. CTA acknowledges the possible dangers of alcohol and in no way supports the abuse of this substance. Whiner Senators do exactly as their name implies… they whine!

Creative Team Alpha would like to go on record as saying that the Shiner party is not in any way related to giving someone a black eye. CTA acknowledges the possible dangers of fisticuffs and in no way supports this behavior. Shiner Senators do exactly as their name implies… they shine!</description></topic><topic type="gameplay"><title>Terrible Misfortune Casting</title><description>When a Terrible Misfortune is drawn that has the subtitle Casting, it means that all players with bunnies in The Bunny Circle that have a Senator Bunny Modifier card are allowed to cast a vote as to which bunny in play should be killed. The bunny does not have to belong to the player who drew the Terrible Misfortune card. Only players with bunny Senators may vote (one vote for each bunny Senator that a player owns). If two (or more) bunnies have an equal number of votes against them, then the player who drew the Terrible Misfortune card must cast the deciding or “tie-breaking” vote (even if all of the bunnies involved are his own).

In the event that no Senator votes are cast (no player has a bunny in play with a Senator Bunny Modifier card), then the player who picked the Terrible misfortune (with the Casting subtitle) gets to choose which bunny will be killed (most likely it will be a bunny that belongs to an opponent). Regular Terrible Misfortune cards are still played the same way as before.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1118: Bakery Rolls</title><description>Bakery Rolls may be used once by a player to roll the Brown 12-sided die and to take a number of flavor cards (Chocolate, Caramel Swirl, Pumpkin Spice, Cake Batter, etc.) from the top of the Draw Pile equal to the number rolled. The player does not draw again until he has less than seven cards.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1119: Bunny Bytes</title><description>First, the player reads the entire card text out loud. Next, the player counts down ( 3 – 2 – 1 – Go! ) and announces, “Bunny Bytes”. Bunny Bytes may be used once by the first opponent to show the player a picture of a bunny on their phone to retrieve any bunny from Weil’s Pawn Shop. The player may take any one of the winning opponent’s bunnies already in The Bunny Circle (not the bunny retrieved).</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1120: Freaking Boron</title><description>Freaking Boron may be used once by a player to steal five saved Special or Very Special cards from his opponents. The player may steal all of the cards from one or several different opponents, and may steal less than five cards if he chooses or if five cards are not available.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1130: Order Sorter</title><description>First, the player reads the entire card text out loud. Next, the player counts down ( 3 – 2 – 1 – Go! ) and announces, “Order Sorter”. Order Sorter may be used once by the first opponent to sort the cards in his five-card hand numerically (using the Card Identification Number) to exchange any unwanted cards in his five-card hand for new ones from the Draw Pile. The player may exchange any of the cards in his five-card hand for any cards discarded by the winning opponent.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1131: Rare Perfect Square</title><description>Rare Perfect Square allows the player to roll the dice and to receive one Metal card or coin for each number rolled that is a perfect square ( 1 – 4 – 9 – 16 ). If no Metal cards or coins exist at Morden’s Metals Exchange, then the player is out of luck. Players may not sell their new Metal cards or coins until their next turn.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1132: Sacred Chalice Of Rixx</title><description>Sacred Chalice Of Rixx may be used once by a player to add the current Exchange Rates of the Gold, Silver and Copper at Morden’s Metals Exchange and to spend that amount of Dolla at any open store. Dolla earned with the Sacred Chalice Of Rixx may not be saved. If no stores are open, then the player is out of luck.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1133: Where The Buffalo Roam</title><description>Where The Buffalo Roam may be placed on any player which must feed the buffalo 5 units of any food (Cabbage, Water, Radish or Milk – in any combination) or lose a Carrot (return it to any Kaballa’s Market). Where The Buffalo Roam continues visiting one player per round counter-clockwise around The Bunny Circle. If Where The Buffalo Roam encounters a player that has no food to offer, or not enough food, then it starves and is eliminated (discarded). Where The Buffalo Roam may be eliminated using any weapon.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1135: Cow By A River</title><description>Cow By A River may be used once by a player to roll the die and to take a number of Water and Milk units equal to the number rolled from the discard piles. The units may be all Water, all Milk or a combination of both that total the number rolled.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1137: Marvin Gardens</title><description>Marvin Gardens may be used once by a player to roll the die and to take a number of Cabbage and Radish units equal to the number rolled from the discard piles. The units may be all Cabbage, all Radish or a combination of both that total the number rolled.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1141: Cherry Cordial</title><description>Cherry Cordial may be given to all players simultaneously once a curse word is heard during play and forces the first player that utters the next curse word to discard one saved card of each category (if he has one): Special, Very Special, Zodiac, Mysterious Place, Bunderground Station and Relative. May be used at any time!

A curse (or naughty) word can only be defined by the people playing the game. Since words change from group to group, country to country and language to language, it is impossible to provide a list of these words. Each group will have to decide for itself which words are not allowed.</description></topic></topics></deck>
