<deck><topics><topic type="gameplay"><title>Chinese Zodiac Die</title><description>If a C appears in one of the die boxes of a card, then the player using the card must roll the Chinese Zodiac die.</description></topic><topic type="gameplay"><title>Chinese Zodiac Cards</title><description>When you draw a Chinese Zodiac card, you must immediately place it face up in front of you and draw another card. Chinese Zodiac cards may not be kept in your hand. I a player is given a Chinese Zodiac card during the initial deal at the start of the game, or picks one from the Draw Pile during play, then the card is saved and the player draws another card. This is very similar to how players save Kaballa Dolla. Many new cards will refer to these saved Chinese Zodiac cards during play.

At the end of the game (before The Magic Carrot is revealed), the small deck of Zodiac Cards, hidden away at the start of the game, is inspected. The small Zodiac Card at the bottom of the deck is considered the Winning Zodiac sign. If a player has the large Zodiac card saved with the Winning Zodiac sign, then he is awarded the following special privileges:

1. The player may move any one bunny in The Bunny Circle from any one player to any other player.  This may effectively eliminate a player from reaching the final draw of The Magic Carrot (if he has only one bunny in The Bunny Circle at the end of the game), or it may allow a player with no bunny in The Bunny Circle a chance at the final draw of The Magic Carrot.

2. If the Winning Zodiac sign is the player’s birth zodiac sign or the current zodiac sign, then the player may also take any three Carrots from the opponent with the most Carrots. If two or more opponents have the same amount of Carrots, then the player may choose from which opponent he will take the three Carrots.

3. If the Winning Zodiac sign is both the player’s birth zodiac sign and the current zodiac sign, then the player may take almost all of the Carrots from all of his opponents. Each opponent that had at least one Carrot must be left with only one Carrot, the rest of the Carrots will belong to the player.

It is possible that when the game ends no player is holding the Winning Zodiac sign. If this is the case, then the game simply continues by revealing The Magic Carrot using the small deck of Carrot Cards.

Each Chinese Zodiac card shows the years for its sign. If a player has three consecutive saved Chinese Zodiac cards (by year), then he may play two cards per turn.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Law Enforcement Bunny</title><description>A player with a Law Enforcement Bunny in The Bunny Circle cannot have any of his saved objects stolen or traded without his consent. A Law Enforcement Bunny may be combined with another Law Enforcement Bunny to form a Bunny Triplet.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1173: Dates And Smoked Salmon</title><description>
  Dates And Smoked Salmon may be used once by a player to roll the dice and to spend an amount of Dolla at any open store equal to the number rolled on the Brown die if it matches either of the two Zodiac numbers rolled. Each Zodiac sign has a corresponding number. If the number rolled on the Brown die matches both of the two Zodiac numbers rolled, then the player may spend twice the amount.

  Chinese Zodiacs / Zodiacs (Green Booster Deck)

  1. Snake / Aries
  2. Horse / Taurus
  3. Goat / Gemini
  4. Monkey / Cancer
  5. Rooster / Leo
  6. Dog  / Virgo
  7. Pig  / Libra
  8. Rat  / Scorpio
  9. Ox / Sagittarius
  10. Tiger / Capricorn
  11. Rabbit / Aquarius
  12. Dragon / Pisces</description></topic>
<topic type=""><title>1174: Falcon Fracas</title><description>Falcon Fracas may be used once by a player to attack all of the opponents’ Chinese Zodiac cards. Opponents must roll the die once for each Chinese Zodiac card they have saved. Determine which was the last year that the Chinese Zodiac was current (all of the years are printed on the cards) and subtract it from the current year. Next, add it to the number rolled on the Brown die and if the combination is higher than 12, then the opponent may keep the Chinese Zodiac card.

For example, let’s say Carol is an opponent and she is trying to defend the Ox Chinese Zodiac card (last current in 2009), and the current year is 2018. When she subtracts these dates, she will get a 9. Therefore, if Carol can roll a 4 or higher on the Brown die, then she may keep her saved Ox Chinese Zodiac card. If Carol rolls a number lower than 4, then the Falcon steals the Ox Chinese Zodiac card and gives it to the player.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1175: Fargans</title><description>Fargans may be used once by a player to force any opponent to state the last year that the Chinese Zodiac sign rolled was valid and to make the sound of the animal shown or give the player two of his bunnies in The Bunny Circle. The opponent may choose which two of his bunnies in The Bunny Circle he will give to the player. When Fargans is announced, players may either flip their saved Chinese Zodiac cards face down or help the opponent by showing them the dates on their cards. All players are encouraged to grant a generous amount of leeway when judging mimicked animal sounds.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1177: General Tso</title><description>General Tso may be given to any player who places General Tso in his area of The Bunny Circle. Since it is a Roaming Red Run card, General Tso visits one player per round clockwise around The Bunny Circle forcing players to return Carrots if the symbol rolled matches any of their saved Chinese Zodiac cards.

While General Tso is visiting, any player with at least one saved Chinese Zodiac card must roll the Chinese Zodiac die. If the symbol rolled is the same as any of the player’s saved Chinese Zodiac cards, then the player must return a number of Carrots to any Kaballa’s Market equal to the number of bunnies that he has in The Bunny Circle (including General Tso).

In addition to their Roaming Red Run capabilities, General Tso (and Lieutenant Tang) are also a double Yellow bunny and may be combined with another Yellow (or half Yellow) bunny to form a Bunny Triplet. General Tso may be attacked and eliminated using any Weapon card. The player who launched General Tso rolls for his defense against a Weapon card even if the same player also launched the weapon. Each of the General’s chicken regiment acts like a Lucky Clover or Lucky Horseshoe and lowers the level of any weapon used against him.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1180: Leaping Lizards</title><description>Leaping Lizards may be used once by a player to challenge any opponent who has a Leaping saved Chinese Zodiac card. The Leaping Chinese Zodiac cards are: Monkey, Rat and Dragon (because they are always current during a Leap Year). Both players roll the Green die and if the player can roll a higher number than the opponent, then he may steal the Leaping Chinese Zodiac card. If it is currently a Leap Year (2020, 2024, 2028, 2032, 2036, 2040, 2044, 2048…), then the player may re-roll the Green die if his first roll was too low.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1185: Swordfish Of Damocles</title><description>Swordfish Of Damocles may be used once by a player and given to the opponent who has the most Carrots. If the opponent rolls the digits of the current year on any combination of the dice, then he loses all of his Carrots. A roll of 10 is used as a Zero, and rolls of 11 and 12 do not count at all. All Carrots are returned to any Kaballa’s Market. If no opponent has the most Carrots, then Swordfish Of Damocles must be discarded. Any player(s) with a matching pair of saved Atomic Pastry may use (discard) them to eliminate Swordfish Of Damocles before the opponent is forced to roll the dice.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1186: Two-Kilo Mockingbird</title><description>Two-Kilo Mockingbird may be used once by a player to steal any four saved Zodiac cards (from any opponents), and any four Carrots (from any opponents or any Kaballa’s Market), if he can roll any combination of numbers that multiply to 2,000. All four dice must be multiplied. Each die may be rolled up to three times.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1188: Yeti Spaghetti</title><description>Yeti Spaghetti may be used once by a player to roll the first die (Violet) and to take the Carrot from any opponent with the same number rolled. The player may roll the next die (Orange), add the number rolled to the first die and take another Carrot from any opponent with the same number rolled in total. The player may roll the next die (Green), add the number rolled to the first two dice and take another Carrot from any opponent with the same number rolled in total and so on. No Carrots may be taken from any Kaballa’s Market. If any two dice roll the same number, then all of the Carrots are returned and the player loses a bunny. The player may stop rolling dice at any time.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1193: Bad Mood Ood</title><description>Bad Mood Ood may be used once by a player to eliminate either Banned From Argo, Zero Zero, any Exchange card (a card with the word Exchange in the title) or all Roaming Red Run cards in play. May be used at any time!</description></topic></topics></deck>
