<deck><topics><topic type="gameplay"><title>50/50 Weapons</title><description>When a player places a 50/50 Weapon on an opponent’s bunny in The Bunny Circle, the opponent must guess which of two dice he will roll higher. If the opponent guesses correctly, then his bunny will survive. If the opponent guesses incorrectly, then his bunny will die (discarded). If the same number appears on both dice, then the opponent must roll both dice again.

A 50/50 Weapon Ultimate may be given to any player and puts all of his bunnies at risk.</description></topic><topic type="gameplay"><title>Pink Box With Pink Circle</title><description>All cards that have a Pink rectangular box on the left border of the card are considered to be Aggressive cards with the exception of Choose A Carrot (any amount of Carrots) cards. To play an Aggressive card, you must have a bunny in The Bunny Circle.

All cards that have a Pink rectangular box with a Pink circle are also considered to be Aggressive cards and players must still have a bunny in The Bunny Circle to play these cards. This icon will appear only on Special cards. If a player wishes to save (and keep) these Special cards then he must have (and maintain) a bunny in The Bunny Circle. If at any time the player does not have a bunny in The Bunny Circle, then the card is immediately discarded.</description></topic><topic type="gameplay"><title>Zero Value (Small Cards)</title><description>When a player draws a Zero Value small card (Cabbage, Water, Radish, Milk or Defense) it is, as the name implies, worth nothing. These cards may be immediately discarded by the player who is free to feel horrible and cheated… but that’s the way the carrot snaps sometimes!</description></topic><topic type="gameplay"><title>Negative Two (Small Cards)</title><description>When a player draws a Negative Two small card (Cabbage, Water, Radish, or Milk) not only does he gain no supply, but he must give back (discard) 2 units of that supply if he has 2 units to give. If a player does not have 2 units to give, then he is in the clear and will not owe those units later.</description></topic><topic type="gameplay"><title>Forever (Small Cards)</title><description>When a player draws a Forever small card (Cabbage, Water, Radish or Milk) it is, as the name implies, an endless amount of that supply. The player may use or give away any amount of his Forever supply, but keep in mind that trading may only occur during either of the player’s turns that are involved in the trade. Since most Feed The Bunny cards come due during the needy player’s turn, the trading rule is usually accommodating. Please note that cards such as: Maggots, Drought, Starving Snails and Sour Hour which eliminate all of one supply will also eliminate Forever supplies.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Anvil</title><description>Anvil may be placed on any bunny in The Bunny Circle who holds the Anvil. The two adjacent bunnies leave the game for two rounds of play. When the two adjacent bunnies return to The Bunny Circle, the bunny in between them is crushed by the Anvil and discarded.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Blake Take</title><description>Blake Take may be used once by a player to liberate (take) seven cards in total from play. Cards may be taken from any player’s saved Special or Very Special cards or randomly chosen from any player’s five-card hand. The player may choose to liberate his own cards. All cards may be taken from a single player, or a combination of several players. All liberated cards are discarded. Starting with the player who played Blake Take and proceeding in the order of play, all players who had cards taken from their five-card hand must draw new cards from the Draw Pile.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Furry Wall</title><description>Furry Wall may be used once by a player to make any three of his adjacent bunnies in The Bunny Circle into a Bunny Triplet. The Furry Wall card is placed underneath the three bunnies which can be any type of bunny (single kind, single color, half color, Specialty, Super and Celebrity). If any of the three bunnies is moved for any reason, abducted or killed, then the Bunny Triplet is broken and Furry Wall is discarded.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Jay Is Okay</title><description>Jay Is Okay may only be used once by a player whose first name starts with the letter J to take one Carrot, one Weapon and one bunny from Kaballa’s Market, Rooney Weapons Emporium and Weil’s Pawn Shop respectively if their stores are open. The player may only take items from the stores that are open.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Pillars Of Gulu</title><description>Pillars Of Gulu may be used once by a player to steal one bunny and one Carrot from any one opponent. The player may not steal a bunny from one player and a Carrot from another player. The Pillars, bunny and Carrot start in the center of the table and become the property of the first player to roll a 7 on any die, for any reason, on his own turn.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Guardin’ Gnome </title><description>Guardin’ Gnome may be placed under any bunny in The Bunny Circle. If the player’s bunny is attacked and killed, then Guardin’ Gnome immediately attacks any one of the opponent’s bunnies. The player chooses which of the opponent’s bunnies, and that bunny must roll higher than 9 to survive. After the attack, Guardin’ Gnome is discarded.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>High Rollers</title><description>High Rollers may be used once by a player to choose a Carrot if he can stack all eight 12-sided dice in 12 seconds or less. No opponent may disrupt the player either physically or verbally.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Make It Sow</title><description>Make It Sow may be used once by a player to take Cabbage Units or Radish Units (or a combination of both) from any open store that total the number rolled on either die. If the same number appears on both dice then the player receives no supplies.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Paparazzi</title><description>Paparazzi may be used once by a player to scare off (discard) all Celebrity bunnies (and Super Celebrity bunnies) in The Bunny Circle.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Pawn Cloning</title><description>Pawn Cloning may be used once by a player to clone a Pawn. The new Pawn gives the player all of the privileges of the first Pawn. Pawn Cloning moves with the Pawn if it is traded or stolen, but is discarded if the Pawn is returned to Weil’s Pawn Shop.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Six Plosion</title><description>Six Plosion may be used once by a player to collect and redistribute all players’ Top and Bottom Run cards if the total numbers on the dice is a multiple of 6. The player reads through the cards first and then replaces the cards in any positions that he wishes. The player may keep the best cards for himself. When the Top and Bottom Run cards have been restored for all of the players, then play continues.

Multiples of 6: 6, 12, 18, 24, 30, 36, 42, 48, 54, 60, 66, 72, 78, 84, 90, 96</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Transmogrifier</title><description>Transmogrifier may be placed on any bunny which must roll higher than 9 to survive. If the bunny does not survive, then the player may take Water Units or Milk Units (or a combination of both) from any open store that total the number rolled on the die by the opponent.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Fat Bunny Sings</title><description>Fat Bunny Sings may be used once by a player to place any one Aggressive card (a card with a Pink Rectangular Box) from his hand off to the side and to use it just after the last Carrot is claimed but before any of the small cards (Mysterious Place, Zodiac or Carrot) are revealed. The player must still have a bunny in The Bunny Circle to use the Aggressive card.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Trip’s Trips</title><description>Trip’s Trips allows a player to play an extra card every turn for each Bunny Triplet that he has in play (no limitations). If at any time the player has no bunnies in The Bunny Circle, then Trip’s Trips is immediately discarded. Other situations (such as owning certain groups of Zodiac cards) do not allow the player to play extra cards.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>For The King</title><description>For The King may be used once by a player to immediately sacrifice any one of his actual Pawns to eliminate any weapon targeting one of his own bunnies. The Pawn is returned to Weil’s Pawn Shop and may be purchased again. Any card representing a Pawn (Pawn Cloning) may not be used. May be used at any time!</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Ultimate Chaos</title><description>Ultimate Chaos forces all players to discard their Top and Bottom Run cards, and their five-card hands. All bunnies remain in The Bunny Circle. All saved cards (Special cards, Very Special cards, Kaballa Dolla cards, Carrot cards, Zodiac cards and Mysterious Place cards) and supplies (Cabbage Units, Water Units and Defense Units) remain. All players draw new cards, discarding any Play Immediately or Rank cards, saving any Kaballa Dolla cards, placing two cards down as the Top and Bottom Run cards, and keeping five cards in their hands.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Barrier</title><description>Barrier may be placed between any two players and stops weapons that affect adjacent bunnies. For example, the effects of a Nuclear Warhead may not reach your bunny if there is a Barrier between it and the target bunny in The Bunny Circle.

Barrier reverses the direction of Roaming Red Run cards (such as Cyber Bunny or Cruise Missile Prime). Barrier will cause any Roaming Run card to move in the opposite direction after it is reversed. Barrier does not stop any multi-target, non-Roaming Red Run card circumstances. More than one Barrier may be placed side by side between the same two players.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Blinky Madison</title><description>Blinky Madison may be used once by a player to challenge an opponent for a saved Carrot. The player chooses the opponent’s Carrot. Both players look directly at each other and after a countdown from three, the last player to blink takes the Carrot.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Dollar Make Me Holler</title><description>The player holding the US Dollar bill (any denomination) with the highest serial number may take any one saved Special or Very Special card from any opponent and the Carrot with the same city identification letter from an opponent or any Kaballa’s Market.

The serial number is an eight-digit number printed twice on the front of every US Dollar bill. The city identification letter is a large single letter printed inside a black circular design on the left side of the front of every US Dollar bill.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Fantastic Fez</title><description>Fantastic Fez may be placed under any bunny and allows the player to roll the d10 dice anytime that he rolls any of the d12 dice that match in color and to choose which number to use.

The diamond shaped icons indicate the five d10 dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow and Blue) that came in the KinderBunnies game. The player may continue to use the d10 dice until such a time when the bunny with the Fantastic Fez is abducted or killed.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Gazpacho Soup</title><description>Gazpacho Soup may be used once by a player and given to any opponent who must immediately attempt to kill one of his own bunnies. The opponent may use only the cards from his five-card hand. These cards may be weapon cards or other cards that kill bunnies during the same turn (not Feed The Bunny cards). If the opponent has exhausted all of his options and none of his bunnies has been killed, then the opponent must discard the remaining cards in his five-card hand and all of his bunnies (including Holographic) in The Bunny Circle. Bunnies with a Heavenly Halo or Angel Wings Bunny Modifier remain. The opponent must draw five new cards from the Draw Pile.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Text Time</title><description>All opponents may send the player a text message of this card title. The opponent whose text arrives last loses his next turn. If a number of players are unwilling or unable to send a text message within one minute, then they all lose their next turns.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Out Of Harm’s Way</title><description>Out Of Harm’s Way may be used once by a player to immediately move a bunny out of harms way to any position in The Bunny Circle if it will be affected by a range weapon or if it will become the next target of a Roaming Red Run card. Directly targeted bunnies cannot be moved. May be used at any time!</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Dated Kaballa Dolla</title><description>When a player draws the Dated Dolla card, he must immediately spend an amount of Dolla equal to the date (01 – 31) at any open store. Dated Dolla may not be saved. If no stores are open, then the player is out of luck.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Random Kaballa Dolla</title><description>When a player draws the Random Dolla card, he must roll the Clear 20-sided die immediately and spend the amount of Dolla rolled at any open store. Random Dolla may not be saved. If no stores are open, then the player is out of luck.</description></topic></topics></deck>
