<deck><topics><topic type="cardtype"><title>Half Color Bunnies</title><description>Half color bunnies may be used to form Bunny Triplets by their type, or either of their two colors.</description></topic><topic type="cardtype"><title>Zodiac Cards</title><description>When you draw a Zodiac card, you must immediately place it face up in front of you and draw another card. Zodiac cards may not be kept in your hand. If a player is given a Zodiac card during the initial deal at the start of the game, or picks one from the Draw Pile during play, then the card is saved and the player draws another card. This is very similar to how players save Kaballa Dolla. Many new cards will refer to these saved Zodiac cards during play.

Each Zodiac card shows not only the beginning and end dates for its sign, but the name of the zodiac sign that appears previously and afterwards on the calendar. Also, each Zodiac card has a type or symbol: Air, Earth, Fire or Water. These zodiac symbols are indicated in the upper left corner of the card by the icons: Cloud, Planet, Flame and Waves respectfully. If a player has three consecutive saved Zodiac cards (by date), or all three Zodiac cards of the same symbol, then he may play two cards per turn.

At the end of the game (before The Magic Carrot is revealed), the small deck of Zodiac Cards, hidden away at the start of the game, is inspected. The small Zodiac Card at the bottom of the deck is considered the Winning Zodiac sign. If a player has the large Zodiac card saved with the Winning Zodiac sign, then he is awarded the following special privileges:

1) The player may move any one bunny in The Bunny Circle from any one player to any other player.

This may effectively eliminate a player from reaching the final draw of The Magic Carrot (if he has only one bunny in The Bunny Circle at the end of the game), or it may allow a player with no bunny in The Bunny Circle a chance at the final draw of The Magic Carrot.

2) If the Winning Zodiac sign is the player’s birth zodiac sign or the current zodiac sign, then the player may also take any three Carrots from the opponent with the most Carrots. If two or more opponents have the same amount of Carrots, then the player may choose from which opponent he will take the three Carrots.

3) If the Winning Zodiac sign is both the player’s birth zodiac sign and the current zodiac sign, then the player may take almost all of the Carrots from all of his opponents. Each opponent that had at least one Carrot must be left with only one Carrot, the rest of the Carrots will belong to the player.

It is possible that when the game ends no player is holding the Winning Zodiac sign. If this is the case, then the game simply continues by revealing The Magic Carrot using the small deck of Carrot Cards.</description></topic><topic type="weapon"><title>Snowball</title><description>Snowball may be placed on any bunny in The Bunny Circle which must roll higher than 13 on the Clear 20-sided die to survive. If the bunny survives, then Snowball moves to the next bunny clockwise in The Bunny Circle and increases in strength to Level 14. Each time that Snowball moves to the next bunny, the level of the weapon will increase by one until a bunny dies.

Snowball is played during one player’s turn, and no Barrier can stop Snowball.</description></topic><topic type="weapon"><title>Seventh Whisk</title><description>Seventh Whisk may be placed on any bunny in The Bunny Circle which must roll higher than 1 on each of the seven 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow, Blue, Black and Red) to survive. A Defense Card of 7 Units or higher is needed to eliminate this weapon.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Day Of The Dead</title><description>Day Of The Dead may be used once by a player to revive three bunnies from the Discard Pile if he can roll a 6 on at least three of the seven 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow, Blue, Red and Pink – Perfectly Pink Booster Deck). Each die may be rolled three times. The bunnies revived must match the color of the dice that rolled a 6. For example, if a player rolled a 6 on the Yellow, Orange and Blue dice, then he may revive a Yellow, Orange and Blue bunny if they exist in the Discard Pile. If only one or two of the colors are present in the Discard Pile, then a player may revive just one or two bunnies. Half color bunnies may be revived as well provided that at least one of the colors match. Free Agent, Specialty bunnies and Celebrity bunnies (Ominous Onyx Booster Deck) may not be revived using this card. The maximum number of bunnies that a player may revive is three. Extra rolls of 6 may give a player more color choices, but not more bunnies.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Fingercuffs</title><description>Fingercuffs may be used once by a player to connect the fate of any two adjacent bunnies in The Bunny Circle. Place the card between any two bunnies. The bunnies share all Bunny Modifiers. If one bunny is killed, then the other one dies as well. Bunnies separated by a Barrier may not be joined. Any object (a bunny, a Barrier or The Djarnak) placed between two joined bunnies breaks the connection and discards the Fingercuffs.</description></topic><topic type="market"><title>High-Low Cash</title><description>High-Low Cash may be used once by a player to roll the Blue and Red 12-sided dice and the Clear 20-sided die, subtract the lowest number rolled from the highest number rolled, and immediately spend that amount of Dolla at any open store.

If all of the stores are closed, then the player is out of luck and the Dolla amount is forfeited.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Leif Carrotson</title><description>Leif Carrotson may be given to any player whose bunnies all join Leif Carrotson and roam the board clockwise. Leif Carrotson and the abducted bunnies visit one player per round of play who rolls the three 12-sided dice (Violet, Red and Black). The player’s action is determined by the highest die roll:

Red die high = The player takes one bunny from Leif Carrotson and places it anywhere in The Bunny Circle.

Violet die high = The player takes nothing. Leif Carrotson and the bunnies keep roaming.

Black die high = The player throws one bunny overboard (discarded).

Just like all Roaming Red Run cards, if Leif Carrotson hits a Barrier, it will reverse direction and will visit the same player on two consecutive turns. When Leif Carrotson has no bunnies left onboard, he is discarded.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Precession</title><description>Precession may be used once by a player to roll the eight 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow, Blue, Black, Red and Zodiac) as many times as the numerical value of the current month. If the zodiac sign rolled is either the player’s birth zodiac sign or the current zodiac sign and the numbers 2, 1, 6 and 10 appear on at least one die each, then the player takes all of the remaining Zodiac cards from the Draw Pile.

For example, if it is currently September, then the player is allowed to roll the dice nine times since September is the ninth month. After each roll, if the zodiac sign rolled is either the player’s birth zodiac sign or the current zodiac sign, and the numbers 2, 1, 6 and 10 appear on at least one die each, then the player will take all of the remaining Zodiac cards from the Draw Pile. While rolling for Precession, a player may not save a die roll from one attempt to the next. All dice must be rolled for each attempt. Since the current age in the zodiac is Pisces, any player rolling the Pisces zodiac sign during any attempt will win Precession automatically regardless of the outcome of the other seven 12-sided dice.

If you are still playing Killer Bunnies® and the Quest for the Magic Carrot in the year 2060, the automatic win zodiac sign will change to Aquarius. Please note that the exact date for the ‘Dawning of the Age of Aquarius’ is not known with any certainty. So please accept the year 2060 as our best bunny guess.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Wheels Chocolate</title><description>Wheels Chocolate may be used once by a player to roll the eight 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow, Blue, Black, Red and Pink – Perfectly Pink Booster Deck) and to take the top three cards from the Draw Pile that have the same color back as the highest die rolled. If two or more dice roll equally high, then the player may choose three cards of each color from the Draw Pile. A player must save all Kaballa Dolla and Zodiac cards, and use all Play Immediately cards. By the end of his turn, the player must discard any surplus cards from his hand so that he once again has a five-card hand and two cards down (the Bottom and Top Run cards).</description></topic><topic type=""><title> Zodiac Terminator</title><description>Zodiac Terminator may be used once to roll the seven 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow, Blue, Red and Zodiac) and the Clear 20-sided die and to force the player with the saved Zodiac card that matches the zodiac sign rolled on the Zodiac die to discard all of his possessions (five-card hand, two down cards, saved cards and Carrots), draw seven new cards and start the game over if any other die roll matches the current day of the month. All of the player’s Carrots are returned to Kaballa’s Market (even if the market is closed), and all other cards are placed in the Discard Pile. Zodiac Terminator cannot be played after the 20th day of any month since no die rolled for this card has more than twenty sides.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Gift Certificate Kaballa’s Market</title><description>This Gift Certificate may be used only at Kaballa’s Market (if the market is open). The Dolla amount is determined by the roll of the Yellow 12-sided die and must be spent immediately.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>La Tape Worm</title><description>LA Tape Worm may be used once by a player to double the amount of Cabbage Units needed on any pending Feed The Bunny card on any bunny in The Bunny Circle. The LA stands for Los Angeles.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Albino Baby 5000</title><description>Albino Baby 5000 protects any one player’s bunnies from Plutonium, Quite Irascible Diffractable Cheese Balls and Bittersweet Chocolate Covered Anti-Matter Raisins for the duration of the game providing that this card is a saved Very Special. May be used at any time!</description></topic><topic type="veryspecial"><title>Operation Spoilsport</title><description>Operation Spoilsport may be used once by a player to immediately duplicate a consequence of death of his bunnies in The Bunny Circle against the bunnies of the responsible opponent. May be used at any time!

Operation Spoilsport may be used by a player to avenge only his own bunny (or bunnies). Any consequence of death suffered by the player’s bunny (or bunnies) in The Bunny Circle will also be suffered by the opponent’s bunny (or bunnies) in The Bunny Circle. For example, let’s suppose that an opponent kills a player’s bunny with a Leviathan. The player may use Operation Spoilsport to automatically kill one of the opponent’s bunnies. The player must, however, use Operation Spoilsport before the next player starts his turn. For another example, if the opponent uses the Sea Whiz Mount on the player and kills three of his bunnies, then the player may immediately use Operation Spoilsport to kill up to three of the opponent’s bunnies (if the opponent has three bunnies in The Bunny Circle).</description></topic><topic type="immediate"><title>Community Carrot</title><description>Every player with at least one saved Zodiac card may choose a Carrot from Kaballa’s Market (if the market is open). The player who drew Community Carrot chooses the first Carrot, and then Carrots are chosen in a clockwise direction by each qualifying player. If the market runs out of Carrots before each player gets to choose, then the rest of the players are out of luck and the game is over. It is rare (but possible) for the game to end using Community Carrot and for no player to have a bunny in The Bunny Circle. If this should happen, then all players will pretend to have a bunny, the Winning Zodiac sign is not drawn, and the Magic Carrot is revealed.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>End Of Game</title><description>The game is over when the last Carrot is chosen or purchased from the market. If a player used his TOP RUN card to finish the game, then he does not draw a replacement card.

At this point, the small deck of Zodiac Cards, hidden away at the start of the game, is inspected. The small Zodiac Card at the bottom of the deck is considered the Winning Zodiac sign. 

It is possible that when the game ends no player is holding the Winning Zodiac sign. If this is the case, then the game simply continues by revealing The Magic Carrot using the small deck of Carrot Cards.

If a player has the large Zodiac card saved with the Winning Zodiac sign, then he is awarded the following special privileges:

1) The player may move any one bunny in The Bunny Circle from any one player to any other player.

This may effectively eliminate a player from reaching the final draw of The Magic Carrot (if he has only one bunny in The Bunny Circle at the end of the game), or it may allow a player with no bunny in The Bunny Circle a chance at the final draw of The Magic Carrot.

2) If the Winning Zodiac sign is the player’s birth zodiac sign or the current zodiac sign, then the player may also take any three Carrots from the opponent with the most Carrots. If two or more opponents have the same amount of Carrots, then the player may choose from which opponent he will take the three Carrots.

3) If the Winning Zodiac sign is both the player’s birth zodiac sign and the current zodiac sign, then the player may take almost all of the Carrots from all of his opponents. Each opponent that had at least one Carrot must be left with only one Carrot, the rest of the Carrots will belong to the player.

If at this point, a player has no bunnies in The Bunny Circle, then that player cannot win the game.  He must give all of his Carrots away to the player that has at least one bunny in The Bunny Circle and the most KABALLA DOLLA saved.

To determine the winner, retrieve the small deck of Carrot Cards that you put aside at the start of the game. The last card in the deck (the bottom card) is the Magic Carrot for this particular game and the player holding the Carrot with the matching picture is the winner. Just for fun, go through the small deck of Carrot Cards one card at a time from the top to the bottom. This builds the suspense. Try it. It’s fun!</description></topic><topic type="run"><title>The Mystery Urn</title><description>The player holding The Mystery Urn rolls the Violet 12-sided die. The next player clockwise must roll higher than the highest roll (so far) or that player must donate a card to the kitty. The kitty is simply a pile of cards collected during The Mystery Urn activity.  The cards that can feed the kitty are bunnies from The Bunny Circle, saved Carrots, or saved Zodiac cards.

Play continues clockwise. Each player who has at least one pertinent card must play. The first player to roll a 12 wins the kitty. However, the player who started The Mystery Urn activity will get a final chance to roll a 12 and win the kitty.

If a player gives up his last pertinent card, then he is finished with The Mystery Urn activity and cannot win the kitty.

If all players have lost all of their pertinent cards, then no player wins. All of the Carrots are returned to Kaballa’s Market (even if the market is closed) and the other cards are discarded.

If the initial roll by the player is a 12, then The Mystery Urn activity is over and no one wins anything.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Bunny Booster</title><description>Bunny Booster may be placed under any bunny and changes its color to Red. Bunnies that become Red will inherit the special feature for that type of bunny. Bunny Booster may be placed under single color or half color Congenial, Gleeful, Lumbering, Sinister and Timid bunnies (but not Super bunnies).</description></topic></topics></deck>
