<deck><topics><topic type=""><title>Enlisted Rank Cards</title><description>Enlisted Rank cards are numbered (E-1 to E-6). E-1 is the lowest rank and E-6 is the highest rank. Although many bunnies in The Bunny Circle may carry a Rank card (either Enlisted or Officer), only the highest Enlisted ranked bunny (HERB) and the highest Officer ranked bunny (HORB) will be given a special privilege.

The special privilege awarded to the player who owns the highest Enlisted ranked bunny (HERB) is the ability to play an extra card directly from his five-card hand each turn. The card may be played at the start, middle or end of the player’s turn. If the card is a Run card, then the player may use or discard it. If the card is a Special (or Very Special) card, then the player may use or save it. A player who obtains the HERB may use the special privilege during the turn it was acquired. A player who has the second highest Enlisted ranked bunny is encouraged to kill the HERB so that he may obtain the special privilege for himself.

If any bunnies in The Bunny Circle have Officer ranks, then the player who owns the HERB must ask the permission of the player who owns the HORB to use the special privilege. If the player who owns the HORB replies in the negative, then the player who owns the HERB loses the special privilege for one round of play. The player who owns the HERB may ask permission each round of play, but the decision to allow him the special privilege, or to disallow him the special privilege, lies solely with the player who owns the HORB at the time.

If at any time, no bunnies with Officer ranks are in The Bunny Circle, then the player who owns the HERB may use the special privilege without asking anyone’s permission.

The Highest Enlisted Ranked Bunny card should always be placed on top of the HERB to denote which player is awarded the special privilege and to act as a bulls-eye. A Clear stand is provided to keep the card in place.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Officer Rank Cards</title><description>Officer Rank cards are numbered (O-1 to O-6). O-1 (pronounced oh-one) is the lowest rank and O-6 is the highest rank. Although many bunnies in The Bunny Circle may carry a Rank card (either Enlisted or Officer), only the highest Enlisted ranked bunny (HERB) and the highest Officer ranked bunny (HORB) will be given a special privilege.

The special privilege awarded to the player who owns the highest Officer ranked bunny (HORB) is the ability to play an extra card directly from his five-card hand each turn. The card may be played at the start, middle or end of a player’s turn. If the card is a Run card, then the player may use or discard it. If the card is a Special (or Very Special) card, then the player may use or save it. A player who obtains the HORB may use the special privilege during the turn it was acquired. A player who has the second highest Officer ranked bunny is encouraged to kill the HORB so that he may obtain the special privilege for himself.

If any bunnies in The Bunny Circle have Officer ranks, then the player who owns the HERB must ask the permission of the player who owns the HORB to use the special privilege. If the player who owns the HORB replies in the negative, then the player who owns the HERB loses the special privilege for one round of play. The player who owns the HERB may ask permission each round of play, but the decision to allow him the special privilege, or to disallow him the special privilege, lies solely with the player who owns the HORB at the time.

If at any time, no bunnies with Officer ranks are in The Bunny Circle, then the player who owns the HERB may use the special privilege without asking anyone’s permission.

The Highest Officer Ranked Bunny card should always be placed on top of the HORB to denote which player gets the special privilege and to act as a bulls-eye. A Clear stand is provided to keep the card in place.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Dated Feed The Bunny</title><description>The amount of Cabbage Units and Water Units that a bunny must feed is the same as the last digit of the day of the month when the game is being played. For example, if a player uses a Dated Feed The Bunny on Valentine’s Day, then the amount of Cabbage Units or Water Units that the opponent will need to feed will be 4 Units (since Valentine’s Day is always on the 14th of February). Any bunny belonging to a player born on the 17th of any month must double the amount of Units needed to Feed The Bunny.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Half Red Bunnies</title><description>Half Red Congenial Bunny: may feed 1 Cabbage Unit and 1 Water Unit per turn. Supplies may not be saved to another turn. The 1 Cabbage Unit and 1 Water Unit are for the exclusive use of this bunny and may not be shared with other bunnies in The Bunny Circle.

Half Red Gleeful Bunny: The player with this bunny in The Bunny Circle may spend 1 Dolla per turn at any open store. Dolla may not be saved to another turn.

Half Red Lumbering Bunny: has a Single Lucky Clover which lowers the level of any weapon used against this bunny by one.

Half Red Sinister Bunny: is protected by a Hemi-Bounce Force Field which protects it from any weapon with original weapon levels (1-6). The bunny is affected normally by weapons with a weapon level higher than 6.

Half Red Timid Bunny: The player with this bunny in The Bunny Circle may re-roll any one die one time during his turn only.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Army Of The 12 Bunnies</title><description>Army Of The 12 Bunnies may be placed on any bunny in The Bunny Circle which must roll higher than the numerical value of the current hour on the Yellow 12-sided die to survive. All players are encouraged to use an AM/PM system of time measurement to determine the hour of play (from 1 to 12). Regardless of the outcome of the first bunny’s roll, the Army is moved immediately to the next bunny clockwise and the hour number is lowered by one. The next bunny must also roll the Yellow 12-sided die. The Army Of The 12 Bunnies is played entirely during one player’s turn and ends when the hour number is zero, or when there are no more viable bunny targets in The Bunny Circle. Army Of The 12 Bunnies is not impeded by a Barrier. Since the Army is not a weapon, Clovers cannot lower its effect, and Defense Cards cannot be used to stop an attack.</description></topic><topic type=""><title> Athena</title><description>Athena may be used once by a player to purchase a Green item from any opponent for 5 Dolla: a Green bunny in The Bunny Circle, a Green Pawn or a saved Earth symbol Zodiac card. The opponent is given the 5 Dolla.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>B-Flat</title><description>Players must remove their front door key from any chain or ring before playing B-Flat. When all players are ready, a countdown from three will begin the contest. The first player to balance their front door key on any edge may choose a Carrot from Kaballa’s Market (if the market is open).</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Better Bunny Booster</title><description>Better Bunny Booster may be placed under any bunny and changes its color to Pink. Bunnies that become Pink will inherit the special feature for that type of bunny. Better Bunny Booster may only be played on single (or half) color Congenial, Gleeful, Lumbering, Sinister, and Timid bunnies. Bunny Booster and Better Bunny Booster may not occupy the same bunny at the same time.</description></topic><topic type=""><title> Bunny Dearest</title><description>Bunny Dearest may only be placed on a single color bunny in The Bunny Circle (no half color bunnies) which must roll higher than the numerical value of the current month using the same color 12-sided die as the target bunny to survive. For example, if a player placed Bunny Dearest on a Violet Timid Bunny during the month of September (the 9th month), then the opponent would have to roll higher than 9 on the Violet 12-sided die for the bunny to survive. If the player had the Violet Pawn, then he would be entitled to a re-roll of the Violet 12-sided die. The opponent may not use Roll-A-Lution to improve his chances since the Clear 20-sided die has no color.

In addition to the initial attack, all other bunnies in The Bunny Circle of the same color (or half color) as the target bunny must also roll the same die to survive. To continue our example, all other Violet bunnies (or half Violet bunnies) in The Bunny Circle would also have to roll higher than 9 on the Violet 12-sided die to survive.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>The Bunnymooners</title><description>The Bunnymooners must be used by (or given to) any player who has been playing Killer Bunnies for less than a year. The player may choose a Carrot from Kaballa’s Market (if the market is open) or take a Carrot from any opponent.

If the player of the card is not a Bunnymooner, then he must give the card to the first Bunnymooner in the current direction of play. If no person playing the game is a Bunnymooner, then the player of the card may choose a Carrot from Kaballa’s Market (if the market is open) or take a Carrot from any opponent. If Kaballa’s Market is closed, then the Carrot may only be taken from an opponent.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Bunnyshop Quartet</title><description>Bunnyshop Quartet may be used once by a player to take any Pawn from Weil’s Pawn Shop (if the shop is open), or any opponent that has the same color as any of the eight 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow, Blue, Black, Red and Pink) that rolled a 4.</description></topic><topic type=""><title> Ice Nine</title><description>Ice Nine may be given to any player who must keep the card until he plays any other card that requires the rolling of one or more dice (not including the Zodiac die). All rolls of any die or dice will automatically have a value of 9 for the other card.

For example, if an opponent gives a player Ice Nine, then that player could play the card Supplies Surprise. Since all five 12-sided dice have a value of 9, the player would take all five supplies (Cabbage, Water, Dolla, Carrot and a bunny). Ice Nine is discarded after one use.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Joint Custody</title><description>Joint Custody may be used once by a player to share ownership and privileges of any opponent’s bunny. A player that has no bunnies in The Bunny Circle may place Joint Custody under an opponent’s bunny and still be allowed to play Aggressive cards such as weapons and Choose A Carrot. Joint Custody is discarded when the bunny is moved to another player in The Bunny Circle, traded with another player, abducted or killed.

A player with Joint Custody of an opponent’s bunny is also the owner of the bunny. Therefore, any card that affects the player’s bunny (or bunnies) will affect the bunny in Joint Custody. A bunny in Joint Custody may be used to win the game.</description></topic><topic type=""><title> Locked In</title><description>Locked In may be used once by a player to force any opponent to play his Top and Bottom Run cards on his next turn or turns. All cards that can be used, must be used, even if the consequences are bad for the opponent. If the Top or Bottom Run card was a Special or Very Special card that could not be used at the time of play, then they must be discarded.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>The Lonely Ranger</title><description>The Lonely Ranger is a Blue bunny that is also a Roaming Red Run card which means that he will move to a new player every round of play in a counter-clockwise direction. As the player receives The Lonely Ranger, he may place him in any position among his bunnies in The Bunny Circle.

Like all Roaming Red Run cards, The Lonely Ranger will move at the end of the turn of the player who introduced him to The Bunny Circle. Also, The Lonely Ranger changes direction when encountering a Barrier and is discarded if he encounters a Neutronium Barrier.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Mad Bunny Disease</title><description>Mad Bunny Disease may be given to any player whose bunnies in The Bunny Circle all become infected. The player must return one Carrot to Kaballa’s Market (even if the market is closed) at the start of each of his turns while he has Mad Bunny Disease. If the player adds bunnies to The Bunny Circle during play, then they will also become infected. To discard Mad Bunny Disease, the player must first eliminate all of his bunnies from The Bunny Circle.

If a bunny is traded to another player or changes owners in The Bunny Circle, then all of the other players’ bunnies will also become infected with Mad Bunny Disease. It is possible for more than one player’s bunnies to become infected with Mad Bunny Disease. Once a player has returned all of his Carrots to Kaballa’s Market, he will still have to eliminate all of his bunnies from The Bunny Circle before he can discard Mad Bunny Disease.

A bunny that is abducted by the Beyea Aliens is returned free of Mad Bunny Disease. A bunny that is abducted by any other card will still have Mad Bunny Disease and may spread it to other players’ bunnies. Any two bunnies that share the Fingercuffs will also share Mad Bunny Disease. Sunny Day may be used once to eliminate Mad Bunny Disease from all bunnies in The Bunny Circle.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Q.C.P. (Quantum Chromodynamic Pulse)</title><description>Quantum Chromodynamic Pulse may be used once to force all players that have a Free Agent or Double Free Agent bunny in The Bunny Circle to roll the five 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow and Blue). The bunny becomes the color (or colors) of the highest die (or dice) rolled. If two or more colors roll equally high, then the bunny will become more than one color. Use the colored Chips to keep track of the color(s) of the bunnies.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Refried Peas</title><description>Refried Peas may be used once by a player to take any P-Card from the Discard Pile. The card must be used immediately if it is a Run card, or it may be saved if it is a Special card.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Thirty Helens</title><description>Thirty Helens may be used once by a player to take any weapon from Rooney’s Weapons Emporium and launch it immediately if the total on any of the 12-sided dice rolled adds to thirty. Thirty Helens cannot be used if Rooney’s Weapons Emporium is closed. No person who has the letters H-E-L-E-N (yes, you will need two Es) anywhere in their full name may be directly targeted by the weapon taken with Thirty Helens.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Truth Or Hare</title><description>Truth Or Hare may be given to any opponent with at least one bunny in The Bunny Circle who must state the title of his Top Run card. If the opponent can deceive the player, then he will take a bunny. If the opponent cannot deceive the player, then he will give up a bunny. Four possible outcomes exist:

1) The opponent is telling the truth and the player believes him.

2) The opponent is telling a lie and the player does not believe him.

3) The opponent is telling the truth and the player does not believe him.

4) The opponent is telling a lie and the player believes him.

For outcomes 1 and 2, the player chooses which bunny to take from the opponent. For outcomes 3 and 4, the player chooses which bunny to give to the opponent.</description></topic><topic type=""><title> Venus Cycle</title><description>Venus Cycle may be used once by a player to choose a Carrot from Kaballa’s Market (if the market is open) if at least one 8 is rolled on any of the eight 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow, Blue, Black, Red and Pink). More than one roll of 8 does not allow a player to choose more than one Carrot. If the current year is 2009, 2017, 2025, 2033, 2041 or any 8th year thereafter, and at least one 8 is rolled on any of the eight 12-sided dice, then the player may choose four Carrots.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Get Out Of Death Free</title><description>Get Out Of Death Free may be used once by a player to bring any one bunny back to life immediately. Must be used during the same turn as the death. May be used at any time!

If the bunny was carrying any Bunny Modifiers, then they are discarded since the bunny was technically dead first, and then brought back to life.</description></topic></topics></deck>
