<deck><topics><topic type="cardtype"><title>Celebrity Bunnies</title><description>Celebrity bunnies have no color (Blue, Green, Orange, Violet or Yellow) or kind (Congenial, Gleeful, Lumbering, Sinister or Timid). Celebrity bunnies are their own kind of bunny. A player may, of course, win the game with one of these bunnies in The Bunny Circle.

Celebrity bunnies come as singles, doubles or triplets that make forming a Bunny Triplet easier. If a player has three single Celebrity bunnies in The Bunny Circle, then he has formed a Bunny Triplet and may play two cards per turn. If a player has a single Celebrity Bunny and a double Celebrity Bunny, then he has also formed a Bunny Triplet and may play two cards per turn. If a player has a triplet Celebrity Bunny in The Bunny Circle, then he automatically has a Bunny Triplet and may play two cards per turn.

If an opponent attacks and kills a Celebrity Bunny, then all bunnies in the double or triplet are lost and the card is discarded. In that respect, Celebrity Bunny doubles and triplets are treated as a single target. When counting for Roaming Red Run cards, and weapons that affect bunnies many spaces away, Celebrity Bunny cards (singles, doubles or triplets) count as one space.</description></topic><topic type="cardtype"><title>Extra Super Bunnies</title><description>Extra Super bunnies give a player the advantages of Super bunnies, and all of the special features of either the Red or Pink bunnies.

The advantages of Super bunnies:

1) The player with a Super Bunny in The Bunny Circle may automatically play two cards per turn.

2) When a Super Bunny is attacked with a Weapon card, the player may roll the Clear 20-sided die regardless of the weapon level. Even though this has no advantage if the weapon level is 13 or higher, it is a great advantage for weapons with levels 1-12.

3) When a Super Bunny is placed in The Bunny Circle, all bunnies that are the same color (or half color) as the Super Bunny are immediately eliminated from The Bunny Circle. Until the Super Bunny itself is eliminated, no bunny of the same color (or half color) can survive in The Bunny Circle.

A Red or Pink bunny that has The Heavenly Halo is not eliminated from The Bunny Circle if a Red or Pink Extra Super Bunny of the same color arrives. If The Heavenly Halo is placed on the Extra Super Bunny, then all bunnies of the same color arriving in The Bunny Circle are safe (not discarded).

Once an Extra Super Bunny has been eliminated, it cannot be purchased from Weil’s Pawn Shop nor can it be brought back into the game for any reason using any card. In addition, an Extra Super Bunny cannot be affected by the cards: Cloning, Bunny Booster, Random Paintball Assault, Better Bunny Booster or Blanch.</description></topic><topic type="cardtype"><title>Gender Weapons</title><description>Gender Weapons come in four categories determined by the words “Guy” (male) and “Gal” (female). If the first word is Guy, then the player using the card must be male. If the second word is Gal, then the opponent must be female. If you have a Gender Weapon in your hand that you cannot play, then you may either trade it to another player, or run it through the Bottom and Top Run card cycle and discard it.

Players may declare themselves male or female before the start of the game if they wish to choose their gender.

Gender Weapons that are reversed, bounced back or otherwise redirected by a player must still follow the gender restrictions. For example, if Tim plays a Guy/Gal weapon on one of Carol’s bunnies, she cannot use Reversal Of Fortune to send it back to Tim since she is not a Guy and he is not a Gal. If a Red Sinister (with a Bounce Back Force Field) is unsuccessfully attacked with a Gender Weapon, then it would only return to one of the attacker’s bunnies if the gender conditions were satisfied.</description></topic><topic type="cardtype"><title>Mysterious Place Cards</title><description>When you draw a Mysterious Place Card, you must immediately place it face up in front of you and draw another card. Mysterious Place Cards may not be kept in your hand. If a player is given a Mysterious Place card during the initial deal at the start of the game, or picks one from the Draw Pile during play, then the card is saved and the player draws another card. This is very similar to how players save Kaballa Dolla and Zodiac cards. Many new cards will refer to these saved Mysterious Place cards during play.

After the initial deal, and once game play begins, any player who draws a Mysterious Place card will take control of the Yellow Ball (with the Red Stripe). The Yellow Ball will always be placed on top of the last Mysterious Place card that was drawn. The player who has control of the Yellow Ball may control the destiny of any card played by any opponent that has a Yellow Ball in the picture. The opponent must play the card first, then the player may redirect it to any other player, bunny or the Discard Pile. Control of the Yellow Ball will always reside with the player who drew the last Mysterious Place card.

At the end of the game (before the Winning Zodiac is revealed), the small deck of Mysterious Place Cards, hidden away at the start of the game, is inspected. The player holding the Mysterious Place card that matches the picture on the small Mysterious Place Card at the bottom of the deck is allowed to steal all saved Zodiac cards of any one type (Air, Earth, Fire, Water) from any opponents.

It is possible that at the end of the game no player is holding the matching Mysterious Place card. If this is the case, then the game simply continues by revealing the Winning Zodiac using the small deck of Zodiac Cards.</description></topic><topic type="cardtype"><title>Unique Bunnies (The Strange Ones)</title><description>Seven unique bunnies have been introduced into the game. Some are new for the Ominous Onyx Booster Deck while others were introduced earlier. All of these bunnies have a particular color, and each bunny has a unique feature. Here is a quick reference guide:

Holographic Bunny (Red) – Can only be killed by certain weapons.

Dago Bunny (Green) – Protects Kinder bunnies.

Pinky Tusca-Hare-O (Pink) – Can change positions in The Bunny Circle.

Lonely Ranger (Blue) – A Roaming Red Run card.

Ambassador Bunny (Violet) – Is placed in an opponent’s area in The Bunny Circle.

Brundle Bunny (Orange) – Is safe from weapons, but feeds double amounts.

Bunny Detroit (Yellow) – Can only be directly targeted by a Mom</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Alliteration Situation</title><description>Alliteration Situation may be used once by a player to take any card from the Discard Pile that has a title beginning with the same letter as the player’s first name. If the title of a card has more than one word, then a player will have to match the first letter of the first word. The card taken must be used immediately.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Ambassador Bunny</title><description>Ambassador Bunny is a Violet bunny that is owned by one player but is placed in any opponent’s area in The Bunny Circle. The bunny is owned exclusively by the first player, and does not allow the opponent (host player) to use the bunny to play Aggressive cards. At the end of the game, Ambassador Bunny may be used by the player to win the game.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Arctic Caribou</title><description>Arctic Caribou may be used once by a player to freeze any opponent’s food supply. Cabbage Units or Water Units as cards or Vouchers that are owned by the opponent at the time that Arctic Caribou is played may not be used to Feed The Bunny or to trade with other players. Cabbage Units or Water Units purchased afterwards will be available to the opponent.

Also, the opponent’s Cabbage Units and Water Units may not be taken for any reason by cards such as Drought, Maggots or Rock Bottom. Arctic Caribou is removed (discarded) once the opponent kills any bunny in The Bunny Circle or in space.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Awesome Recruiter</title><description>Awesome Recruiter may be used once by a player to assign all Rank cards in the Discard Pile to any bunnies in The Bunny Circle. Not all Rank cards in the Discard Pile have to be used if there are not enough bunnies in The Bunny Circle. No Rank card already assigned to a bunny may be removed or exchanged.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Beauty On Duty</title><description>Beauty On Duty may be used once by a player to move any Rank card assigned to any bunny in The Bunny Circle to any female Kinder bunny. The female Kinder bunnies are easy to spot because they are wearing bows.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Bunny Bowling</title><description>Bunny Bowling may be used once by a player to roll the eight 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow, Blue, Black, Red and Pink) and to choose a Carrot from Kaballa’s Market (if the market is open) for each strike (roll of 10) or spare (combination of two dice that add to 10) rolled.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Bunny Budd</title><description>Bunny Budd may be used once by a player to sacrifice one of his Yellow (or half Yellow) Enlisted ranked bunnies to eliminate any Officer ranked bunny in The Bunny Circle. Both bunnies are discarded.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Bunny Detroit</title><description>Bunny Detroit is a Yellow bunny that can only be directly targeted with an Aggressive card by a player who is a Mom. Bunny Detroit may fall victim to a Terrible Misfortune or may be killed by range weapons or Roaming Red Run cards provided that he was not the direct target.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Bunny Tax</title><description>Bunny Tax may be given to any player who must pay 2 Dolla each to keep his bunnies alive or discard them. All bunnies belonging to the player in The Bunny Circle and in space are taxed. Any bunny that cannot be paid for is discarded.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Delinquent Minors</title><description>Delinquent Minors may be used once by a player (under the age of 18) to exchange his entire five-card hand with any opponent. The player must choose the opponent before the exchange.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Echo Valley 2-6809</title><description>Echo Valley 2-6809 may be used once by a player to roll the eight 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow, Blue, Black, Red and Pink) and five 10-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow and Blue – KinderBunnies®) and to take the saved Mysterious Place card of his choice from any opponent if any five of the dice match the last five digits of his phone number. If a player has more than one phone number, then he must declare which number he is attempting to roll before he begins. On the 12-sided dice, a roll of 10 equals a 0 and rolls of 11 or 12 do not count as any number.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>The Fifth Element</title><description>The Fifth Element may be used once by a player to roll the eight 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow, Blue, Black, Red and Pink) and five 10-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow and Blue – KinderBunnies®) and to take any one bunny in The Bunny Circle, saved Zodiac card or Mysterious Place card that has a 5 in the Card Identification Number from any opponent if at least one 5 is rolled. If at least five 5s are rolled, then the player may take all of the bunnies in The Bunny Circle, saved Zodiac cards and saved Mysterious Place cards that have a 5 in the Card Identification Number.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Follow The Queen</title><description>Follow The Queen goes to the player with the saved Mysterious Place card numbered the same as the Violet 12-sided die roll. When a player owns the Queen, none of his bunnies may be attacked directly using an Aggressive card. The Queen moves to the player who owns the saved Mysterious Place card that matches the number rolled each time that the Violet 12-sided die is rolled. The Queen waits in the center of the table if no player has the saved Mysterious Place card that matches the number rolled.

While waiting in the center of the table, the Queen may be attacked using any single target weapon, and any player may roll for her outcome. If the attack is successful, then the Queen is removed (discarded). The Queen may not carry any Bunny Modifiers.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Identity Crisis</title><description>Identity Crisis may be used once to force all players whose birth zodiac sign is the same as the one rolled on the 12-sided Zodiac die to switch positions at the game table exchanging all of their possessions with another player. This may happen to more than two players. For example, if three Scorpios are at the table, and a Scorpio sign is rolled, then all three would have to stand up, abandon all of their possessions, and move to the next Scorpio’s position at the table in the direction of play. Identity Crisis may be stopped by The Magic Spatula. If only one player has the birth zodiac sign rolled, then no switching occurs.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Matrixing</title><description>The player borrows the Blue and Red Pawns from Weil’s Pawn Shop or players, hides one of the Pawns in his left hand, and challenges any opponent for possession of any one of his bunnies in The Bunny Circle. The opponent must choose whether the player is holding either the Blue Pawn or the Red Pawn. If correct, then the opponent keeps his bunny. If incorrect, then the player takes the bunny and places it anywhere in The Bunny Circle. The Blue and Red Pawns are returned to Weil’s Pawn Shop or the players when Matrixing is complete.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>My Big Fat Bunny Wedding</title><description>My Big Fat Bunny Wedding may be used once by a player to force any opponent to share half of his Carrots with his spouse. If there is an odd number of Carrots, then the spouse will get the extra Carrot. To avoid confusion during play, players are encouraged to announce their spouses at the start of the game.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>O-75</title><description>O-75 may be used once to force all players to reveal one card from their five-card hand. The player whose card has the highest Card Identification Number may exchange it for a Carrot from Kaballa’s Market. If the player takes a Carrot, then their revealed card is discarded, and a replacement card is drawn immediately from the Draw Pile. O-75 may not be used if Kaballa’s Market is closed.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Pawn Star</title><description>Pawn Star may be used once by a player to force the opponent with the most Pawns to give them all away to other players. If two (or more) opponents have the same amount of Pawns, then they must both (all) give them away to other players (not each other). If no other players exist, then all of the Pawns are returned to Weil’s Pawn Shop.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Enlisted Rank Cards</title><description>Enlisted Rank cards are numbered (E-1 to E-9). E-1 is the lowest rank and E-6 is the highest rank. Although many bunnies in The Bunny Circle may carry a Rank card (either Enlisted or Officer), only the highest Enlisted ranked bunny (HERB) and the highest Officer ranked bunny (HORB) will be given a special privilege.

The special privilege awarded to the player who owns the highest Enlisted ranked bunny (HERB) is the ability to play an extra card directly from his five-card hand each turn. The card may be played at the start, middle or end of the player’s turn. If the card is a Run card, then the player may use or discard it. If the card is a Special (or Very Special) card, then the player may use or save it. A player who obtains the HERB may use the special privilege during the turn it was acquired. A player who has the second highest Enlisted ranked bunny is encouraged to kill the HERB so that he may obtain the special privilege for himself.

If any bunnies in The Bunny Circle have Officer ranks, then the player who owns the HERB must ask the permission of the player who owns the HORB to use the special privilege. If the player who owns the HORB replies in the negative, then the player who owns the HERB loses the special privilege for one round of play. The player who owns the HERB may ask permission each round of play, but the decision to allow him the special privilege, or to disallow him the special privilege, lies solely with the player who owns the HORB at the time.

If at any time, no bunnies with Officer ranks are in The Bunny Circle, then the player who owns the HERB may use the special privilege without asking anyone’s permission.

If President Ficus is in The Bunny Circle, the player with President Ficus can supercede the HORB’s decision to allow (or not allow) the highest Enlisted ranked bunny (HERB) to play an extra card.

The Highest Enlisted Ranked Bunny card should always be placed on top of the HERB to denote which player is awarded the special privilege and to act as a bulls-eye. A Clear stand is provided to keep the card in place.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Officer Rank Cards</title><description>Officer Rank cards are numbered (O-1 to O-9). O-1 (pronounced oh-one) is the lowest rank and O-6 is the highest rank. Although many bunnies in The Bunny Circle may carry a Rank card (either Enlisted or Officer), only the highest Enlisted ranked bunny (HERB) and the highest Officer ranked bunny (HORB) will be given a special privilege.

The special privilege awarded to the player who owns the highest Officer ranked bunny (HORB) is the ability to play an extra card directly from his five-card hand each turn. The card may be played at the start, middle or end of a player’s turn. If the card is a Run card, then the player may use or discard it. If the card is a Special (or Very Special) card, then the player may use or save it. A player who obtains the HORB may use the special privilege during the turn it was acquired. A player who has the second highest Officer ranked bunny is encouraged to kill the HORB so that he may obtain the special privilege for himself.

If any bunnies in The Bunny Circle have Officer ranks, then the player who owns the HERB must ask the permission of the player who owns the HORB to use the special privilege. If the player who owns the HORB replies in the negative, then the player who owns the HERB loses the special privilege for one round of play. The player who owns the HERB may ask permission each round of play, but the decision to allow him the special privilege, or to disallow him the special privilege, lies solely with the player who owns the HORB at the time.

If at any time, no bunnies with Officer ranks are in The Bunny Circle, then the player who owns the HERB may use the special privilege without asking anyone’s permission.

If President Ficus is in The Bunny Circle, the player with the highest Officer ranked bunny (HORB) must ask permission from the player with President Ficus to play an extra card. President Ficus can supercede the HORB’s decision to allow (or not allow) the highest Enlisted ranked bunny (HERB) to play an extra card.

The Highest Officer Ranked Bunny card should always be placed on top of the HORB to denote which player gets the special privilege and to act as a bulls-eye. A Clear stand is provided to keep the card in place.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>President Ficus</title><description>President Ficus may be placed in The Bunny Circle and attacked in any way that a bunny is attacked (and killed) including weapons and Terrible Misfortune. The player with the highest Officer ranked bunny (HORB) must ask permission from the player with President Ficus to play an extra card. President Ficus can supercede the HORB’s decision to allow (or not allow) the highest Enlisted ranked bunny (HERB) to play an extra card.

Just before the Magic Carrot is revealed, the player with President Ficus can order all bunnies with a Rank card in The Bunny Circle into the Discard Pile. President Ficus itself is not a bunny, and therefore cannot be used to play Aggressive cards or to win the game.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Strawberry Fields</title><description>Strawberry Fields may be used once by a player to change any saved Danish to a Strawberry Tart that may only be used to feed Red, half Red or Pink bunnies. Place Strawberry Fields under the saved Danish (Large Prune, Very Large Prune or Mini) to keep track of its status.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Trading Places</title><description>Trading Places may be used once by a player to force any opponent to exchange two of his saved Mysterious Place cards for one of yours. In order to use this card against an opponent, that player must have at least two saved Mysterious Place cards. Trading Places cannot be used for a one to one exchange. The player chooses all three saved Mysterious Place cards in the exchange.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Two Fish In A Tank</title><description>Two Fish In A Tank may be placed on any saved Mysterious Place card. Because it is a Roaming Red Run card, Two Fish travels counter-clockwise around The Bunny Circle visiting saved Mysterious Place cards in ascending numerical order. For example, if Two Fish start on Mysterious Place card #3, then it would move to Mysterious Place card #4 on the next turn. If no player had Mysterious Place card #4 saved, then Two Fish would move to Mysterious Place card #5 and so on. Once the Mysterious Place card with the highest number is visited, Two Fish will start over with Mysterious Place card #1.

When visited, each Mysterious Place card is destroyed (discarded) unless the player can roll its number on either the Blue 12-sided or Clear 20-sided die, then Two Fish are destroyed (discarded). The player who must roll to protect his saved Mysterious Place card may choose which die to roll. As they travel around The Bunny Circle, Two Fish destroy any Barriers that they encounter between players, but are destroyed themselves by Neutronium Barriers. If at any time, no player has a Mysterious Place card saved, then Two Fish is discarded.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>The White Party</title><description>The White Party may be used once by a player to take The White Stuff, the White Pawn, and all Free Agent and Double Free Agent bunnies in The Bunny Circle. The player may give the items to any opponent or opponents that he wishes or keep them for himself.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Zener Diode</title><description>Zener Diode may be placed on any Roaming Red Run card currently roaming which prevents the card from changing direction when it encounters a Barrier. If it should encounter a Barrier, then Zener Diode and the Roaming Red Run card will remain dormant until the Barrier is either moved, or eliminated (discarded). Zener Diode does not prevent a Roaming Red Run from being destroyed by a Neutronium Barrier.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Abe Froeman</title><description>The player that has this card saved and the Green Pawn doubles the value of all of his Cabbage Units. For example, if a player is asked to feed 4 Cabbage Units and has both Abe Froeman and the Green Pawn, then he will only have to feed 2 Cabbage Units. A player without the half Cabbage Unit must round up to the nearest Cabbage Unit when asked to feed an odd amount of Cabbage.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Incriminating Photos</title><description>The player that has this card saved may control the special privilege (extra card played) every round by the opponent who has the highest Officer ranked bunny (HORB). The player chooses which card in the opponent’s five-card hand to use and how to use it. The opponent can be forced to discard the card, play it against another opponent or even against himself. Every round of play (during the opponent’s turn), the player may use his Incriminating Photos.

If at any time the player has no bunnies in The Bunny Circle, then Incriminating Photos is discarded immediately. Players cannot save this Special without a bunny in The Bunny Circle.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Insurance Porpoises</title><description>Insurance Porpoises may be placed on any bunny along with 5 Dolla. If the bunny is killed, then the player may return it to The Bunny Circle at the start of his next turn and discard both Insurance Porpoises and the 5 Dolla. All Bunny Modifiers remain with the bunny.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Loan Shark</title><description>Loan Shark may be used once by a player to borrow up to 20 Dolla from the Discard Pile. An amount of Dolla equal to 150% of the original loan must be paid back to the Discard Pile before the game ends or the player must forfeit all of his Carrots, saved Zodiac and saved Mysterious Place cards to his oldest opponent in the game.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Mike Post</title><description>The player that has this card saved and the Black Pawn doubles the value of all of his Defense Units. For example, if a player is attacked with a Weapon Level 8 and has both Mike Post and the Black Pawn, then he will only have to use 4 Defense Units to stop the weapon.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Time Worf</title><description>Time Worf may be used once to force all players to move their Top Run card to the next player clockwise and their Bottom Run card to the next player counter-clockwise. If the player decides to use Time Worf right away, he must first slide his Bottom Run card into the Top Run card position and replace his Bottom Run card.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Zan</title><description>The player that has this card saved and the Blue Pawn doubles the value of all of his Water Units. For example, if a player is asked to feed 4 Water Units and has both Zan and the Blue Pawn, then he will only have to feed 2 Water Units. A player without the half Water Unit must round up to the nearest Water Unit when asked to feed an odd amount of Water.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Bunny Bunker</title><description>Bunny Bunker may be used once by a player to protect any one bunny from the effects of a range weapon such as the Nuclear Warhead. The bunny cannot be the direct target of the weapon or connected to the direct target using Fingercuffs. May be used at any time!</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Platinum Rosebud</title><description>Platinum Rosebud may be used once by a player to control the destiny of any opponent’s Top Run card. After the opponent reveals the Top Run card, the player first decides whether the opponent may use it, or if he wishes the opponent to discard it. Next, the player may decide where the card will be placed (if it is a weapon card), or force the opponent to play a dangerous card on one of his own bunnies. Finally, if the card is beneficial, the player may insist that the opponent give the card to him. Platinum Rosebud must be played before the opponent starts his turn. May be played at any time!</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Rerun</title><description>Rerun may be used once by a player to place any one of his bunnies from The Bunny Circle back into his five-card hand and to discard any unwanted card. When bunnies are Rerun, they lose all of their Bunny Modifiers. May be used between any two players turns!</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Dark Violets</title><description>Every player may discard up to three cards from their five-card hand and immediately replace them with new cards from the Draw Pile. Dark Violets cannot be used to force any player to discard any card.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Much More</title><description>Much More may be given to any player that has Much More bunnies, Cabbage Units, Water Units, Carrots, Defense Units, Pawns, saved Zodiac cards, or saved Mysterious Place cards than all of the other players. Much More is defined as more than twice the amount of any opponent. Each of the items listed on the card must be evaluated separately. The player must distribute his possessions equally amongst himself and his opponents. Equally is defined as meaning that each player will receive one item (or Unit) before any player gets a second of the same item (or Unit).

For example, let’s pretend that Carol has been found to have Much More Cabbage (9 Units) and Much More Water (3 Units) than all of her three opponents. If this is true, then Carol must distribute her 9 Cabbage Units amongst four players (including herself). All four players will receive 2 Cabbage Units first, and one player will get an extra Unit. Carol is allowed to choose which player (including herself) will receive the extra Cabbage Unit. Carol must also distribute her 3 Water Units. She may keep 1 Water Unit for herself and give the other 2 Water Units away to different players. One player will not receive a Water Unit.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>End Of Game</title><description>The game is over when the last Carrot is chosen or purchased from the market. If a player used his TOP RUN card to finish the game, then he does not draw a replacement card.

At this point (before the Winning Zodiac is revealed), the small deck of Mysterious Place Cards, hidden away at the start of the game, is inspected. The player holding the Mysterious Place card that matches the picture on the small Mysterious Place Card at the bottom of the deck is allowed to steal all saved Zodiac cards of any one type (Air, Earth, Fire, Water) from any opponents.

It is possible that at the end of the game no player is holding the matching Mysterious Place card. If this is the case, then the game simply continues by revealing the Winning Zodiac using the small deck of Zodiac Cards.

Next, the small deck of Zodiac Cards, hidden away at the start of the game, is inspected. The small Zodiac Card at the bottom of the deck is considered the Winning Zodiac sign. 

It is possible that when the game ends no player is holding the Winning Zodiac sign. If this is the case, then the game simply continues by revealing The Magic Carrot using the small deck of Carrot Cards.

If a player has the large Zodiac card saved with the Winning Zodiac sign, then he is awarded the following special privileges:

1) The player may move any one bunny in The Bunny Circle from any one player to any other player.

This may effectively eliminate a player from reaching the final draw of The Magic Carrot (if he has only one bunny in The Bunny Circle at the end of the game), or it may allow a player with no bunny in The Bunny Circle a chance at the final draw of The Magic Carrot.

2) If the Winning Zodiac sign is the player’s birth zodiac sign or the current zodiac sign, then the player may also take any three Carrots from the opponent with the most Carrots. If two or more opponents have the same amount of Carrots, then the player may choose from which opponent he will take the three Carrots.

3) If the Winning Zodiac sign is both the player’s birth zodiac sign and the current zodiac sign, then the player may take almost all of the Carrots from all of his opponents. Each opponent that had at least one Carrot must be left with only one Carrot, the rest of the Carrots will belong to the player.

If at this point, a player has no bunnies in The Bunny Circle, then that player cannot win the game.  He must give all of his Carrots away to the player that has at least one bunny in The Bunny Circle and the most KABALLA DOLLA saved.

Just before the Magic Carrot is revealed, the player with President Ficus can order all bunnies with a Rank card in The Bunny Circle into the Discard Pile. President Ficus itself is not a bunny, and therefore cannot be used to play Aggressive cards or to win the game.

To determine the winner, retrieve the small deck of Carrot Cards that you put aside at the start of the game. The last card in the deck (the bottom card) is the Magic Carrot for this particular game and the player holding the Carrot with the matching picture is the winner. Just for fun, go through the small deck of Carrot Cards one card at a time from the top to the bottom. This builds the suspense. Try it. It’s fun!</description></topic><topic type="run"><title>The Mystery Urn</title><description>The player holding The Mystery Urn rolls the Violet 12-sided die. The next player clockwise must roll higher than the highest roll (so far) or that player must donate a card to the kitty. The kitty is simply a pile of cards collected during The Mystery Urn activity.  The cards that can feed the kitty are bunnies from The Bunny Circle, saved Carrots, saved Zodiac cards, or Mysterious Place cards.

Play continues clockwise. Each player who has at least one pertinent card must play. The first player to roll a 12 wins the kitty. However, the player who started The Mystery Urn activity will get a final chance to roll a 12 and win the kitty.

If a player gives up his last pertinent card, then he is finished with The Mystery Urn activity and cannot win the kitty.

If all players have lost all of their pertinent cards, then no player wins. All of the Carrots are returned to Kaballa’s Market (even if the market is closed) and the other cards are discarded.

If the initial roll by the player is a 12, then The Mystery Urn activity is over and no one wins anything.</description></topic><topic type="veryspecial"><title>Guardian Angle</title><description>Guardian Angle may be used once by a player to eliminate any Terrible Misfortune including Very and Extremely Terrible Misfortune. May be used at any time!</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Blown Trojan</title><description>Blown Trojan may be used once by a player to either force The Trojan Bunny in The Bunny Circle to explode immediately or to revive one bunny from the Discard Pile for every two of his bunnies in The Bunny Circle of the same color.

For example, a player with two Orange bunnies in The Bunny Circle may revive any one bunny from the Discard Pile (and immediately place it down next to his other bunnies in The Bunny Circle). A player with three Green bunnies in The Bunny Circle may not pair up the middle one twice to revive two bunnies. However, a player with four Blue bunnies in The Bunny Circle may revive two bunnies from the Discard Pile. Remember that Specialty bunnies and Celebrity bunnies  have no color and cannot be used to revive bunnies with Blown Trojan.

A player may revive any bunny from the Discard Pile (including Free Agent, Holographic, Specialty and Celebrity bunnies) regardless of the color of the bunnies used to revive it.</description></topic></topics></deck>
