<deck><topics><topic type="gameplay"><title>Weil’s Pawn Shop</title><description>Any player may buy supplies anytime during his turn at Weil’s Pawn Shop (if the shop is open). The supplies that are sold at the shop are: Pawns (which give players three advantages), and used bunny cards (which may be run and returned to The Bunny Circle). A player does not need a bunny in The Bunny Circle to buy supplies from Weil’s Pawn Shop.

Weil’s Pawn Shop is open at the start of the game. Run cards exist that either change the prices at Weil’s Pawn Shop, or close the shop. The shop does not need to be closed first to change the prices using a Weil’s Pawn Shop card. New prices are listed on these cards

A player may purchase Pawns and used bunny cards at Weil’s Pawn Shop. During regular play, bunnies will now be discarded in a separate pile near the Weil’s Pawn Shop Starter Card, and will remain face up. Players may purchase any discarded bunny for 10 Dolla (including Free Agent, Holographic, Specialty and Celebrity bunnies – Ominous Onyx Booster Deck). Bunnies may not be placed directly into The Bunny Circle, but must be run through the Bottom Run and Top Run card cycle.

If the game runs long, and the players need to reshuffle the Discard Pile to make a new Draw Pile, then the discarded bunnies at Weil’s Pawn Shop must be included as well.

If a player purchases a bunny from Weil’s Pawn Shop he may find himself with an extra card in his five-card hand. If this is the case, then the player must choose and remove any unwanted card from his five-card hand, and place it directly into the Discard Pile before ending his turn.

Cards such as Supplies Surprise, The Magic Fountain and Day Of The Dead (Green Booster Deck) will now revive bunnies from Weil’s Pawn Shop. Even if Weil’s Pawn Shop closes and players cannot buy bunnies, the bunny Discard Pile is always open. Cards that revive bunnies will always work just as they have in the past.</description></topic><topic type="gameplay"><title>Pawns</title><description>When a player buys a Pawn from Weil’s Pawn Shop, it gives him three advantages in the game:

1) A Pawn can act as a third colored bunny to create a Bunny Triplet that allows players to play two cards per turn. For example, if a player has two Blue bunnies in The Bunny Circle and the Blue Pawn, he has created a Bunny Triplet and may play two cards per turn. A Pawn itself is not an actual bunny. If a player has just a Pawn (or Pawns), then he may not play Aggressive cards or win the game.

2) A Pawn of a specific color allows a player to re-roll the 12-sided die of the same color during any action in the game. For example, if a player has the Violet Pawn, and Cyber Bunny attacks one of his bunnies, then he may re-roll the Violet 12-sided die to survive Cyber Bunny if the first roll was too low. Players may only use the Pawn re-roll option for cards that ask a player to roll a die (or dice) of a specific color. When using a card that requires more than one die to be rolled, a player may only re-roll the dice that are the same color as the Pawns that he owns.

Players do not have to re-roll any die if they are happy with their first roll of a die. In our example, if the player rolled high enough to survive the Cyber Bunny attack, then he would not have to (and should not want to) re-roll the Violet 12-sided die. A player that has the Red Timid Bunny in The Bunny Circle and who owns Pawns, may re-roll dice (the same color as the Pawns) two times.

3) A Pawn allows a player to use special P-Cards twice before discarding them. P-Cards have the capital letter P built into the outside design of the card.

P-Card Legend:

Violet: Large (and Very Large) Prune Danish

Orange: The Magic (and Incredibly Magic) Fountain

Green: Carrot Top Casino (and Casino Royale)

Yellow: H.E.M.P. and Heavenly Halo Handoff (Twilight White Booster Deck)

Blue: Supplies (and Super Supplies) Surprise

Red: The Mad, Mad (and Monumentally Mad) Donnelaith Bakery

Two Pawns will join the game in later booster decks:

Black: 50/50 Weapons (Twilight White Booster Deck)

Pink: Bingo Flamingo (Perfectly Pink Booster Deck)

P-Cards may be used twice by a player in the same turn, or during two different turns. After a P-Card has been used, place the colored Pawn on top of the card to indicate that it has been used once. After a P-Card has been used twice, discard the card (but save the Pawn, of course).</description></topic><topic type="weapon"><title>Boomerang</title><description>Boomerang may be placed on any bunny in The Bunny Circle which must roll higher than 13 on the Clear 20-sided die to survive. If the opponent’s bunny survives, then he may place the Boomerang onto one of the player’s bunnies (who initially launched the Boomerang) and back and forth until a bunny dies. Once chosen, the targeted bunnies on both the opponent and player’s side cannot change during the exchange.</description></topic><topic type="weapon"><title>C.O.M.A. (Carrot Olfactory Mesmerizing Aroma)</title><description>C.O.M.A. may be placed on any bunny in The Bunny Circle which must roll higher than 17 on the Clear 20-sided die to escape. A bunny in a C.O.M.A. cannot play any Aggressive cards (since it is unconscious), but may be used to win the game (since it is still alive). Bunnies in a C.O.M.A. may still be attacked and killed by any opponent. Red and Pink bunnies (Perfectly Pink Booster Deck) in a C.O.M.A. still have their special feature active.</description></topic><topic type="weapon"><title>F-18 Hornet</title><description>To use the F-18 Hornet a player must put two of his bunnies from The Bunny Circle into the Hornet before it can roam. Double Free Agents, Specialty Bunny (double or triplet) and Celebrity Bunny (double or triplet – Ominous Onyx Booster Deck) may be used in the Hornet, however, each counts as a single bunny. While these bunnies are away, a player may not use any Aggressive cards unless he has other bunnies in The Bunny Circle. The Hornet visits the first player counter-clockwise (that has at least one bunny in The Bunny Circle) and attacks one of his bunnies. The Hornet continues visiting only players with bunnies in a counter-clockwise direction and only attacks one bunny per player before moving on to the next player.

If any opponent rolls higher than 18 on the Clear 20-sided die, then the Hornet and the bunnies are destroyed. If an opponent survives the attack by using Defense Cards, then the Hornet and the bunnies are not destroyed.

If the Hornet makes it back to the player who initially launched it, then the weapon is discarded and the bunnies are returned to The Bunny Circle. Barriers placed after the launch of the Hornet may prevent it from ever returning to the original player.

If the Hornet has no viable bunny targets left in The Bunny Circle or if the Hornet is confined to an area of The Bunny Circle by two or more Barriers and cannot reach a viable bunny target on the other side, then the Hornet is removed (discarded) and the bunnies are returned to the player and placed in The Bunny Circle. Just like all Roaming Red Run cards, if the Hornet hits a Barrier, it will reverse direction and may affect the same player’s bunnies on two consecutive turns.</description></topic><topic type="weapon"><title>Plutonium Radiation</title><description>Plutonium Radiation may be placed on any bunny in The Bunny Circle which dies immediately. Plutonium Radiation remains in The Bunny Circle in the same place where the first bunny died. Adjacent bunnies to the Plutonium Radiation continue to die for two more rounds at the start of the player’s turn that initially used the card. After the third round of death (the initial placement and two more rounds), Plutonium Radiation is discarded. Clover bunnies (bunnies with Clover cards underneath them) may survive since Clovers lower the level of an attacking weapon. If a bunny does survive (using Clover or Defense), it will have to roll or defend again on the next turn.</description></topic><topic type="bunny"><title>Double Free Agent</title><description>Double Free Agent bunnies may be used by a player as any two bunnies of any two kinds (Congenial, Gleeful, Lumbering, Sinister or Timid) and of any two colors (except Red or Pink). The identity of the two bunnies may be the same or different bunnies. The identity of the two bunnies may change at any time during play as the need arises. Double Free Agent bunnies make forming a Bunny Triplet much easier. A Double Free Agent must be treated as a single target when hit with a weapon or Feed The Bunny card. Double Free Agent bunnies cannot become Specialty bunnies or Celebrity bunnies (Ominous Onyx Booster Deck).</description></topic><topic type="run"><title>Pilfer The Pawn</title><description>Pilfer The Pawn may be used once by a player to roll the eight 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow, Blue, Black, Red and Pink – Perfectly Pink Booster Deck), and to pilfer (steal) the Pawn with the same color as the die with the highest number rolled from any opponent or Weil’s Pawn Shop (even if the shop is closed). If two or more dice roll the highest number, then the player may pilfer more than one Pawn.</description></topic><topic type="special"><title>Carrot Top Royale</title><description>To use Carrot Top Royale, a player must have a bunny in The Bunny Circle because it is an Aggressive card. Carrot Top Royale may be placed on any bunny in The Bunny Circle. The player must choose the bunny that will take the risk for the card. This target bunny can be one of his own bunnies or any opponent’s bunny in The Bunny Circle. The owner of the target bunny rolls the six 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow, Blue and Black), and either reaps the reward of the card or suffers the consequence.

If all of the dice show different numbers, then the player takes one Carrot from Kaballa’s Market (if the market is open) and 10 Dolla from the Discard Pile. If any two dice show the same number (doubles), then the bunny gets snuffed (discarded) by the Casino bosses. The bunny that must be discarded was the one chosen to take the risk.

Royale Optional Gamble: After the initial six dice are rolled, if the player wishes, he may roll the Red 12-sided die. If the Red die does not double (match) any of the other dice rolled, then the player takes another 10 Dolla from the Discard Pile and may revive any two bunnies from the Discard Pile. The revived bunnies must be placed in The Bunny Circle. If, however, the die roll does double (match) one of the other dice, then all of the player’s bunnies in The Bunny Circle die, all of the player’s Carrots are returned to Kaballa’s Market (even if the market is closed), and all of the player’s Dolla is discarded.</description></topic><topic type="special"><title>Free Pawn</title><description>Free Pawn may be used once by a player to take two Pawns from Weil’s Pawn Shop. Free Pawn may not be used if Weil’s Pawn Shop is closed.</description></topic><topic type="special"><title>Half Price Coupon Weil’s Pawn Shop</title><description>Half Price Coupon may be used for one turn by a player to purchase any items at Weil’s Pawn Shop for half price. If the total price of an item or items requires a Half Dolla (Stainless Steel Booster Deck) and no Half Dolla is available, then the player must round up to the nearest Dolla.</description></topic><topic type="special"><title>Incredibly Magic Fountain</title><description>Incredibly Magic Fountain may be used once by a player to choose a number (1-12) and to roll the seven 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow, Blue, Black and Red) and Clear 20-sided die. The number of correct rolls is the number of bunnies that a player may revive from the Discard Pile and immediately place anywhere in The Bunny Circle.

For example, let’s pretend that a fictional player Carol wants to use the Incredibly Magic Fountain card. She will not need a bunny in The Bunny Circle since this is not an Aggressive card. First, Carol will choose her lucky number which is 4. Next, Carol will roll the seven 12-sided dice and the Clear 20-sided die. If a 4 is rolled on any of the dice, then Carol may take any bunny from the Discard Pile and place it anywhere in The Bunny Circle. If Carol rolls two 4s, then she may take two bunnies from the Discard Pile.</description></topic><topic type="special"><title>The Monumentally Mad Donnelaith Bakery</title><description>To use the Monumentally Mad Donnelaith Bakery, a player must have a bunny in The Bunny Circle because it is an Aggressive card. The Monumentally Mad Donnelaith Bakery may be placed on any bunny in The Bunny Circle. The player must choose the bunny that will take the risk for the card. This target bunny can be one of his own bunnies or any opponent’s bunny in The Bunny Circle. 

The owner of the target bunny rolls the Red 12-sided die, and either reaps the reward of the card or suffers the consequence.

10-11-12 = Choose one (roll of 10), two (roll of 11) or three (roll of 12) Carrot(s) from Kaballa’s Market.

7-8-9 = Take three Cabbage Cards and three Water Cards from Kaballa’s Market.

4-5-6 = Feed the bunny 5 Cabbage Units and 5 Water Units!

3 = A bag of sugar is dropped killing the bunny!

2 = A well-thrown pitchfork kills the bunny and adjacent bunnies!

1 = Disaster! Lose (discard) all of your bunnies and return all of your Carrots to Kaballa’s Market (even if the market is closed)!

If the consequence for a bunny is to feed, then it must be done immediately. An opponent with no saved Cabbage Units or saved Water Units will not have the opportunity to buy supplies from Kaballa’s Market since it will not be his turn. Cabbage Cards, Water Cards, and Carrots are taken from Kaballa’s Market (if the market is open).</description></topic><topic type="special"><title>Super Supplies Surprise</title><description>Super Supplies Surprise may be used once by a player to roll the seven 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow, Blue, Black and Red) and the Clear 20-sided die. The color die that has the lowest roll is the supply taken by the player. If two or more dice roll the lowest number, then the player may take more than one supply.

Violet 12-sided die = Take two bunnies from the Discard Pile.

Orange 12-sided die = Take two Carrots from Kaballa’s Market.

Green 12-sided die = Take two Cabbage Cards from Kaballa’s Market.

Yellow 12-sided die = Take 20 Dolla from the Discard Pile.

Blue 12-sided die = Take two Water Cards from Kaballa’s Market.

Black 12-sided die = Take two Defense Cards from Rooney’s Weapons Emporium.

Red 12-sided die = Take two Pawns from Weil’s Pawn Shop.

Clear 20-sided die = Take all of the items listed above.

Cabbage Cards, Water Cards, and Carrots are taken from Kaballa’s Market (if the market is open), Dolla and bunnies are taken from the Discard Pile if they are available, Defense Cards are taken from Rooney’s Weapons Emporium (if the emporium is open) and Pawns are taken from Weil’s Pawn Shop (if the shop is open).</description></topic><topic type="veryspecial"><title>Bunny On The Edge Of Forever</title><description>Bunny On The Edge Of Forever may be used once to force the current player to replay his turn. All cards played during the turn are returned to their starting positions at the beginning of the turn in the same order as they were before the turn began (except for the Bunny On The Edge Of Forever card, which is placed in the Discard Pile). The cards may need to be returned to the Draw Pile, Discard Pile or player’s five-card hands. The current player’s turn starts again. Play may very well continue exactly as it did the first time, unless a player changes his mind about an important decision, or unless a die rolls differently than it did before. May be used at any time!</description></topic><topic type="veryspecial"><title>Uriel’s Machine</title><description>Uriel’s Machine may be used once by a player to counteract any Very Special card. If the current date is an Equinox or Solstice date, then the player is allowed to keep and use the opponent’s Very Special card a second time. May be used at any time!

If players have access to current and accurate astrological data for the year in which they are playing the game then, by all means, use that data to determine the precise Equinox and Solstice dates. If not, then simply use these approximate dates:

Spring Equinox: March 20th

Summer Solstice: June 21st

Autumn Equinox: September 22nd

Winter Solstice: December 21st</description></topic><topic type="immediate"><title>Random Kaballa Dolla</title><description>When a player draws the Random Dolla card, he must roll the Clear 20-sided die immediately and spend the amount of Dolla rolled at any open store. Random Dolla may not be saved. If no stores are open, then the player is out of luck.</description></topic><topic type="run"><title>Holographic Bunny</title><description>Holographic Bunny is a Red Bunny that does not need to feed and cannot be used to win the game since it is not technically alive. This bunny can only be harmed by the Laser Gun, Nuclear Warhead, Miniature Black Hole, Quite Irascible Diffractable Cheese Balls, Bittersweet Chocolate Covered Anti-Matter Raisins, Plutonium, Psychic Waves (Twilight White Booster Deck) and Sharks WFLB (Stainless Steel Booster Deck).

The Holographic Bunny may be transformed into a live bunny by using the Ancient Star Rod. If the Holographic Bunny should become alive, it will be vulnerable to all weapons and Feed The Bunny cards, and may be used to win the game. Regardless of whether the bunny is Holographic or it becomes alive by using the Ancient Star Rod, it is still a Red bunny and can be used to form a Bunny Triplet with other Red bunnies.</description></topic><topic type="veryspecial"><title>Bunnies In Black</title><description>Bunnies In Black protects any one player’s bunnies from alien abductions by the Beyea Aliens or their Mothership for the duration of the game providing that this card is a saved Very Special.

Or Bunnies In Black may be used once by a player to retrieve bunnies safely from the Beyea Aliens. Bunnies retrieved become the property of the player and must immediately be placed in The Bunny Circle. A player must discard the Bunnies In Black card after retrieving bunnies from the Beyea Aliens. May be used at any time!</description></topic></topics></deck>
