<deck><topics><topic type="cardtype"><title>Rank Cards</title><description>When a player draws a Rank card from the Draw Pile he must immediately place it under any bunny in The Bunny Circle. Most likely a player will want to assign that Rank card to one of his own bunnies. A bunny that is carrying The Heavenly Halo may not carry a Rank card. If a player draws a Rank card and has no bunnies of his own, then he must place the Rank card under an opponent’s bunny. If there are no bunnies in The Bunny Circle, then the Rank card is discarded.

If a player is given a Rank card during the initial deal at the start of the game, then he must discard it. Another card should then be chosen from the Draw Pile.

If a player picks a Rank card and wishes to place it under a bunny that already has a Rank card, then he may, but only if he owns the bunny. The other Rank card must then be placed under another bunny. If no other bunny exists in The Bunny Circle, then the Rank card must be discarded. A player may not remove a Rank card from a bunny except when Rank cards are being exchanged as described above. If a bunny is abducted by the Beyea Aliens, or dies, then its Rank card is discarded.</description></topic><topic type="cardtype"><title>Enlisted Rank Cards</title><description>Enlisted Rank cards are numbered (E-1 to E-6). E-1 is the lowest rank and E-6 is the highest rank. Although many bunnies in The Bunny Circle may carry a Rank card, only the highest Enlisted ranked bunny (HERB) will be given a special privilege.

The special privilege awarded to the player who owns the highest Enlisted ranked bunny (HERB) is the ability to play an extra card directly from his five-card hand each turn. The card may be played at the start, middle or end of the player’s turn. If the card is a Run card, then the player may use or discard it. If the card is a Special (or Very Special) card, then the player may use or save it. A player who obtains the HERB may use the special privilege during the turn it was acquired. A player who has the second highest Enlisted ranked bunny is encouraged to kill the HERB so that he may obtain the special privilege for himself.

The Highest Enlisted Ranked Bunny card should always be placed on top of the HERB to denote which player is awarded the special privilege and to act as a bulls-eye. A Clear stand is provided to keep the card in place.</description></topic><topic type="cardtype"><title>Pink Bunnies</title><description>Pink Congenial Bunny: may feed up to 5 Cabbage Units and 5 Water Units per turn. Supplies may not be saved to another turn. The 5 Cabbage Units and 5 Water Units are for the exclusive use of this bunny and may not be shared with other bunnies in The Bunny Circle.

Pink Gleeful Bunny: The player with this bunny in The Bunny Circle may spend 5 Dolla per turn at any open store. Dolla may not be saved to another turn.

Pink Lumbering Bunny: has a Lucky Clover Quindruple which lowers the level of any weapon used against this bunny by five.

Pink Sinister Bunny: is protected by a Bounce Away Force Field. Any weapon that directly targets this bunny, but is not successful, is redirected onto any other bunny in The Bunny Circle.

Pink Timid Bunny: When a player has the Pink Timid Bunny in The Bunny Circle, he may roll the Pink 12-sided die any time that he rolls any other 12-sided die. The player will then choose which of the two dice he will keep and use. This action may be performed multiple times for cards such as Supplies Surprise or The Magic Fountain. The Pink 12-sided die may only be used once per any card consequence.

Substitution capabilities are much better than re-roll capabilities because the player has a choice of two numbers for every roll. When re-rolling dice, a player must keep the second roll and may not ‘go back’ to the first.</description></topic><topic type="roaming"><title>Twister</title><description>Since it is a Roaming Red Run card, Twister continues by attacking one bunny per round of play clockwise around The Bunny Circle. Twister may be played on any single color (or half color) bunny in The Bunny Circle which must roll higher than 14 on the Clear 20-sided die to survive. Once Twister has targeted a particular color of bunny, it will not target that color of bunny again. For example, if Twister starts on a Green Bunny, then all Green (or half Green) bunnies in The Bunny Circle will no longer be targeted. If Twister starts on an Orange/Violet half color bunny, then all Orange (or half Orange), and all Violet (or half Violet) bunnies in The Bunny Circle will no longer be targeted. Twister will skip any bunny that is the same color (or half color) as a bunny it has already visited regardless of whether that bunny survived the attack or died.

Specialty bunnies and Celebrity bunnies (Ominous Onyx Booster Deck) are never viable bunny targets. Free Agent and Double Free Agent bunnies may be targeted by Twister, but only as the initial target of the weapon. This is true because once Twister has targeted any color of bunny, a Free Agent may instantly become one of those colors and avoid becoming a viable bunny target. If the player does attack a Free Agent or Double Free Agent bunny as the first target, then the owner of the bunny must declare its color so that Twister cannot target another bunny of the same color.

If Twister has no more viable bunny targets in The Bunny Circle, then the storm dissipates and it is removed (discarded). If Twister is contained within a section of The Bunny Circle by two Barriers, and that section contains no viable bunny targets, then Twister is also removed (discarded).

Use the colored Chips (Wacky Khaki Booster Deck) to keep track of the colors of the bunnies that Twister has already targeted.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Necro Fasci</title><description>Necro Fasci may be placed on any bunny in The Bunny Circle. The opponent must first roll the Pink 12-sided die to determine the range of the weapon. For example, if the Pink die roll is a 4, then the target bunny and all bunnies within four spaces are killed. Four spaces are counted around The Bunny Circle on both sides of the target bunny. For this example, nine bunnies in The Bunny Circle are affected, and Necro Fasci is placed in the Discard Pile.

There are two ways for an opponent to avoid destruction from Necro Fasci. If the Pink die roll is the same as the numerical value of the current month, then no harm comes to any bunny and Necro Fasci is shuffled back into the Draw Pile. In our example, if the current month was April (the fourth month), then Necro Fasci is neutralized before doing any damage to any bunny in The Bunny Circle.

A player may avoid destruction in a second way. The 12-sided Zodiac die must also be rolled for Necro Fasci. If the zodiac sign rolled is the same as the current zodiac sign, then once again, no harm comes to any bunny in The Bunny Circle, and Necro Fasci is shuffled back into the Draw Pile.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Blanch</title><description>Blanch may be placed under any bunny in The Bunny Circle and removes its color turning it into a Free Agent. Blanch cannot not be used on Specialty bunnies or Celebrity bunnies (Ominous Onyx Booster Deck). Red and Pink bunnies with Blanch lose their special features.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Blue Bunny Group</title><description>Blue Bunny Group may be used once by a player to purchase a Blue item from any opponent for 5 Dolla: a Blue bunny in The Bunny Circle, a Blue Pawn or a saved Water symbol Zodiac card. The opponent is given the 5 Dolla.</description></topic><topic type=""><title> Bunny Gras</title><description>Bunny Gras may be used once by a player to return any number of his Cabbage, Water or Defense Cards to their Draw Piles, reshuffle each pile, and draw the same number and type of cards back if he can roll either three of the same number or three consecutive numbers on the three 12-sided dice (Violet, Green and Yellow).

For example, three consecutive numbers might be 2, 3 and 4. Wrap around numbers such as 12, 1 and 2 are not consecutive.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>The Church Bunny</title><description>The Church Bunny may be used once by a player to force any opponent to take all of his saved Special and Very Special cards off of the table and place them back into his hand. One at a time, the player chooses a card (by pointing) and asks, “Isn’t that Special?” If the card is a Special (or Very Special) card, then the player takes the card and saves it face up on the table for himself. The player is allowed to save all Special (or Very Special) cards that he finds even if they were not initially saved by the opponent. The player continues guessing until he chooses a card that is not a Special (or Very Special) card. The opponent will then replace all of his remaining Special (and Very Special) cards back on the table that were saved before The Church Bunny was played. If the opponent has less than five cards in his hand, then he must draw replacement cards immediately.

Or The Church Bunny may also be used once by a player to eliminate (discard) the Hostile Pentecostal.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Mother Tucker</title><description>Mother Tucker may be used once by a player to force any opponent to return Carrots to Kaballa’s Market (even if the market is closed) if he cannot roll at least one double on the eight 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow, Blue, Black, Red and Pink). The number of Carrots returned to Kaballa’s Market is the same as the highest number rolled on any of the dice.

For example, if a player uses Mother Tucker against an opponent, then the opponent must roll all eight 12-sided dice. If at least two dice show the same number, then the opponent’s Carrots are safe. If no doubles appear, then the opponent must return a number of Carrots equal to the largest number rolled on any of the dice. If the highest roll was an 11, then the opponent will choose eleven of his Carrots to return to Kaballa’s Market. If for example, an opponent has only five Carrots, then he must return all five Carrots to Kaballa’s Market, but will not need to return more Carrots later in the game.

If a player owns Carrot #1 (Tucker), then he may not be targeted with Mother Tucker. Opponents who lose Carrots should feel free to shout the title of this card as loudly as they wish.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Pinky Tusca-Hare-O</title><description>Pinky Tusca-Hare-O is a Pink bunny that has the power to jump over (reposition) herself in The Bunny Circle between any two players’ turns.

This special feature will not allow Pinky to avoid most weapon attacks, but very nicely helps her to avoid Roaming Red Run cards by repositioning herself out of the way before they visit. If Pinky is repositioned into another player’s area of The Bunny Circle, then she will belong to the other player. Pinky may not switch owners more than once per game.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Rank Exchange</title><description>Rank Exchange may be used once by a player to force any opponent to exchange the Rank card under any of his bunnies for the Rank card under any of your bunnies. The player chooses both Rank cards in the exchange.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Tug Of War</title><description>Tug Of War may be used once by a player to challenge any opponent. Both players roll 12-sided dice equal to the number of bunnies that each player has in The Bunny Circle, and add the numbers together to get a total. The player with the lower total loses all of his bunnies to the Discard Pile. If the totals are the same, then neither player loses their bunnies. Double Free Agent, Specialty Bunny (double or triplet) or Celebrity Bunny (double or triplet – Ominous Onyx Booster Deck) cards count as a single bunny, and allow the player a single die roll each for Tug Of War.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Viva Las Vegas</title><description>Viva Las Vegas may be used once by a player to challenge any opponent. The stakes are determined by the player and may be any amount of Dolla, saved Zodiac cards or saved Mysterious Place cards (Ominous Onyx Booster Deck). The opponent may choose which of his saved Zodiac or Mysterious Place cards to gamble.

Starting at the same time, both players begin rolling any three 12-sided dice (not the Zodiac die) as quickly as they can. Players keep all rolls of 7. The first player to get three 7s is the winner, and takes all of the stakes.

For example, suppose that there are four friends seated in alphabetical order: Aaron, Betty, Carol and Dwight. Betty is finishing her turn and Carol is boasting to Aaron that she has a really powerful card coming up next. Aaron may play Temporal Flux after Betty’s turn, skipping Carol and Dwight’s turns and play the next card himself.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Appetite Suppressant</title><description>Appetite Suppressant may be used once by a player to lower the amounts of Cabbage and Water Units on any pending Feed The Bunny card by the amounts rolled on the Green (Cabbage) and Blue (Water) 12-sided dice.

If the amount of Cabbage Units or Water Units becomes a negative number, then the player pays nothing (and receives nothing).</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Bingo Flamingo</title><description>Bingo Flamingo may be used once by a player to steal five Carrots from any opponent if the numbers of those Carrots form an unbroken chain on the Flamingo’s Bingo card. Diagonals do not count.

For example, a player could steal five Carrots from an opponent if he had:

The opponent may keep his Carrots by rolling any of the five numbers of the Carrots on either the Clear 20-sided die or the Pink 12-sided die.</description></topic><topic type=""><title> Paradise Syndrome</title><description>The player with this card saved will be skipped by all Roaming Red Run cards. All Roaming Red Run cards already placed on the player (or his bunnies) are immediately discarded.

If at any time the player has no bunnies in The Bunny Circle, then Paradise Syndrome is discarded immediately. Players cannot save this Special without a bunny in The Bunny Circle. Remember, to save a Special card, a player must run it through the Bottom and Top Run card cycle.

Players cannot save this Special without a bunny in The Bunny Circle. Remember, to save a Special card, a player must run it through the Bottom and Top Run card cycle.

Paradise Syndrome may also be used once by a player to eliminate the Stray Asteroid. This card must be a saved Special to be used immediately. Unlike Very Special cards, Paradise Syndrome may not be used to save other players’ bunnies from harm. This card is for the exclusive use of the player who has it saved.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Pink Slip</title><description>Pink Slip may be used once by a player to slip the Pink rectangular box off of any card. Since the card is no longer an Aggressive card, it may be played without a bunny in The Bunny Circle. May be used at any time!</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Transcendental Run</title><description>Transcendental Run may be used once by a player to transform any Run card in his five-card hand into a Very Special card. Since both Transcendental Run and the Run card will both be Very Special cards, they may be used at any time!</description></topic><topic type=""><title> Vel Crows</title><description>Vel Crows may be used once by a player to stop any action of any single card that moves one or more of his bunnies from their place in The Bunny Circle. Vel Crows cannot be used to save bunnies that are killed or discarded. Vel Crows must be used during the same turn that the bunny was taken. May be used at any time!</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Famine Pestilence And Death</title><description>Every player without a saved Zodiac card must immediately feed one of their bunnies in The Bunny Circle 1 Cabbage Unit and 1 Water Unit. Famine Pestilence And Death does not affect players with no bunnies in The Bunny Circle. Each player may choose which bunny to feed. If you have the Red or Pink Congenial Bunny, Holographic Bunny or a bunny with The Heavenly Halo, then you may choose one of these bunnies since they do not need to feed.</description></topic></topics></deck>
