<deck><topics><topic type="gameplay"><title>Breakdown Bunny</title><description>Breakdown Bunny may be placed into The Bunny Circle as a single color bunny the same color as illustrated in the picture. A Breakdown Bunny may be used to form a Bunny Triplet with any two bunnies of the same color (or half color). Three Breakdown Bunny cards also form a Bunny Triplet.

Breakdown Bunny may breakdown (share) the strength of a Weapon or Feed The Bunny card used against it between itself and adjacent bunnies. The adjacent bunnies to the Breakdown Bunny may belong to the player or an opponent.

A Breakdown Bunny must be the direct target of the weapon in order to use its break down abilities.

A Breakdown Bunny cannot break down damage from a weapon directly targeting another bunny. Any bunny positioned adjacent to a Breakdown Bunny must roll for the break down damage separate from other damage caused by the weapon.

For any one weapon or Feed The Bunny card, a Breakdown Bunny may break down the effect only once.

The player may choose which bunny is assigned which weapon strength number. Remember, the three weapon strength numbers (with a maximum difference of 1) must add to the total weapon strength. Each bunny must roll individually to survive using the die indicated on the weapon card. If less than three bunnies are present in The Bunny Circle or an adjacent bunny is separated by a Barrier, then a Breakdown Bunny must take the full weapon strength itself.

For a Weapon card, the strength of the weapon is divided by three. If the weapon strength is not evenly divisible by three, then break down the number into three integral numbers (with a maximum difference of 1) that add to the weapon strength (don’t use fractions). For example, a weapon strength of 10 should break down to 4-3-3.

Using the same division rules, Feed The Bunny cards work in a similar fashion to the weapon cards, with the total amounts being divided between three adjacent bunnies (with a maximum difference of 1 for each food unit individually) during the turn in which the Feed The Bunny card was played. Again, the player may choose which bunny is assigned which amounts to feed. If less than three bunnies are present in The Bunny Circle, then a Breakdown Bunny must feed the full amounts of a Feed The Bunny itself.

A Breakdown Bunny placed adjacent to another Breakdown Bunny may cascade the affect of Weapon and Feed The Bunny cards.

EXAMPLE

Let’s say our fictional player Carol has two bunnies in The Bunny Circle. On the left she has a Green Spiffy Bunny, and on the right she has a Blue Breakdown Bunny. The player to Carol’s right is Tim, and he also has two bunnies in The Bunny Circle; an Orange Gleeful Bunny on the left, and a Violet Evil Bunny on the right.

Now let’s suppose that Carol’s Blue Breakdown Bunny is hit with a level 9 weapon. Carol breaks down the weapon strength so that the Green Spiffy Bunny, the Blue Breakdown Bunny and the Orange Gleeful Bunny are each hit with a level 3 weapon.

But what if Tim’s Orange bunny was a Breakdown Bunny instead of a Gleeful Bunny? If that were true, then the level 3 weapon hit on the Orange Breakdown Bunny would further be broken down so that the Orange Breakdown Bunny would have a level 1 weapon hit, the Blue Breakdown Bunny would have an additional level 1 weapon hit (for a total of 4), and the Violet Evil Bunny would have a level 1 weapon hit.</description></topic><topic type="gameplay"><title>Double Metal Alloy</title><description>Double Metal Alloy cards may be bought from or sold to Morden’s Metals Exchange at the exchange rate of either of the two metals. The metal must be declared by the player (buying or selling) and that declaration must remain in place for a player’s entire turn. Therefore, a player may not sell a Double Metal Alloy at one price and then buy it back at another price during the same turn.

The Double Metal Alloys are: Billon (Copper/Silver), Electrum (Silver/Gold) and Tumbaga (Gold/Copper).</description></topic><topic type="gameplay"><title>Traded Markers</title><description>Trading may only occur during either of the player’s turns that are involved in the trade. Any player may trade: Cabbage Units, Water Units, Radish Units, Milk Units, Kaballa Dolla or Metal cards in any amounts agreed upon by the players. Saved Special cards, saved Very Special cards, Carrots, Zodiac cards, Mysterious Place cards, Bunderground Station cards, Relative cards or bunnies in The Bunny Circle may only be traded once in a game. To keep track of the status of a card, use a TRADED marker. Any player may trade cards from his five-card hand on a one-to-one basis. All players must have five cards in their hand at the end of the trade. Cards in the Top Run or Bottom Run position can never be traded.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1222: Random Ftb</title><description>Random FTB (Feed The Bunny) may be placed on any bunny which must feed the amount shown by the end of its next turn or die. The Green die roll determines the number of Radish Units, and the Blue die roll determines the number of Milk Units.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1232: Banjaxers</title><description>Banjaxers may be used once by a player to replace any bunny in any player’s area of The Bunny Circle. The replaced bunny (and all of its Bunny Modifier cards) is discarded. Banjaxers is a double Violet bunny and may be combined with another Violet (or half Violet) bunny to form a Bunny Triplet.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1233: Banned From Argo</title><description>Banned From Argo may be used once by a player and given to any opponent who must roll the dice and give away any of his bunnies that are the same color (or half color) as both the highest and lowest rolls. If there is a tie for the highest or lowest roll, then the bunnies of all of the colors (or half colors) are given away. The bunnies may be given to any of the players, in any area of The Bunny Circle that the opponent chooses. Those color bunnies will continue to be banned from the opponent’s area of The Bunny Circle until he pays 10 Dolla to the player to remove the card.

Use the colored Chips (Wacky Khaki Booster Deck and Ominous Onyx Booster Deck) to keep track of the opponent’s banned colors.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1240: Market Meltdown</title><description>Market Meltdown may be used once by any player to close Morden’s Metals Exchange and to set all Metal prices to 1 Dolla. New prices may still be set by a player choosing a Carrot. Morden’s Metals Exchange reopens after one round of play starting with the player’s next turn.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1245: Tivy Telos</title><description>Tivy Telos may be used once by a player to end the game immediately if he can roll a 2, 10, 12, or 20 on the 20-sided die. Any opponent may pay the player the amount rolled on the 20-sided die to counteract Tivy Telos and continue the game.

Please note that Tivy Telos requires a player to have two bunnies in The Bunny Circle.

If Tivy Telos is successful, then all Carrots left at any Kaballa’s Market must be given to the player that has at least one bunny in The Bunny Circle and the most Kaballa Dolla saved.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1251: Meek Shall Inherit</title><description>Meek Shall Inherit may be used once by the player with the least number of Carrots (if there is one) to take all of the Carrots from players who do not have at least one bunny in The Bunny Circle. May only be played immediately after the Winning Zodiac is revealed and the results have been implemented. Meek Shall Inherit bypasses the rule that awards the Carrots to the player with the most Kaballa Dolla saved, and therefore must be played before the Magic Carrot is revealed!</description></topic><topic type=""><title>1251: Oh Look, A Butterfly</title><description>Oh Look, A Butterfly may be used once by a player to take up to two Carrots, and up to two Kinder Bunnies in The Bunny Circle, from any opponent who has just sneezed. May be used at any time!</description></topic></topics></deck>
