<deck><topics><topic type="gameplay"><title>Rooney’s Weapons Emporium</title><description>Any player may buy supplies anytime during his turn from Rooney’s Weapons Emporium (if the emporium is open). The supplies that are sold at the emporium are: Defense Cards (which are used by a player to eliminate weapons), and used Weapon cards (which are used by the player to attack an opponent). A player does not need a bunny in The Bunny Circle to buy supplies from Rooney’s Weapons Emporium.

Rooney’s Weapons Emporium is open at the start of the game. Run cards exist that either change the prices at Rooney’s Weapons Emporium, or close the emporium. The emporium does not need to be closed first to change the prices using a Rooney’s Weapons Emporium card. New prices are listed on these cards.

During regular play, Weapon cards will now be discarded in a separate pile face up near the Rooney’s Weapons Emporium Starter Card. Players may purchase any discarded Weapon card for an amount of Dolla equal to the Weapon Level written on the card. Weapons may not be used right away, but must be run through the Bottom Run and Top Run card cycle.

If the game runs long, and the players need to reshuffle the Discard Pile to make a new Draw Pile, then the discarded Weapon cards at Rooney’s Weapons Emporium must be included as well.

If a player purchases a Weapon card from Rooney’s Weapons Emporium, then he may find himself with an extra card in his five-card hand. If this is the case, then the player must choose and remove any unwanted card from his five-card hand, and place it directly into the Discard Pile before ending his turn.

Players may also purchase Defense Cards. These are used to eliminate the effect of a weapon for a particular player. Defense Card Units must match or exceed the level of the weapon that a player wishes to eliminate.</description></topic><topic type="gameplay"><title>Defence Cards</title><description>Players may also purchase Defense Cards. These are used to eliminate the effect of a weapon for a particular player. Defense Card Units must match or exceed the level of the weapon that a player wishes to eliminate.

For example, a Weapon Level 7 may be eliminated by simply using a Defense Card with 7 Units. Another example might be a Weapon Level 8 that may be eliminated by using Defense Cards that add to 8 Units such as a 3 Units and a 5 Units card. In the last example, a player may also use a Defense card that exceeds the weapon level such as an 11 Units card. A player may not take “change” from the Defense Card pile if the Units used to defend against a weapon exceeded the weapon level. Once Defense Cards have been used, they are discarded and may not be sold again. Defense Cards may only be used before a player rolls for the weapon.

Defense Cards protect only one player’s bunnies from harm. When a player uses Defense Cards against a multi-target weapon (such as the Nuclear Warhead), all of the bunnies in The Bunny Circle belonging to that player are protected. Adjacent players may still be affected by the weapon. Adjacent players may, if they have the ability, use their own Defense Cards against the same multi-target weapon.

Any player may use a Defense Card at any time either for himself or another player.

Weapons may be increased in strength by a card (such as The Minilith), or diminished in strength due to increased range from the target bunny (such is the case with the Miniature Black Hole). Regardless of any modification or circumstance, the effects of a weapon are eliminated using Defense Cards that match or exceed the weapon’s original value.</description></topic><topic type="cardtype"><title>Red Bunny Cards</title><description>Red Congenial Bunny: may feed up to 3 Cabbage Units and 3 Water Units per turn. Supplies may not be saved to another turn. The 3 Cabbage Units and 3 Water Units are for the exclusive use of this bunny and may not be shared with other bunnies in The Bunny Circle.

Red Gleeful Bunny: The player with this bunny in The Bunny Circle may spend 3 Dolla per turn at any open store. Dolla may not be saved to another turn.

Red Lumbering Bunny: has a Lucky Clover Triple which lowers the level of any weapon used against this bunny by three.

Red Sinister Bunny: is protected by a Bounce Back Force Field. Any weapon that directly targets this bunny, but is not successful, is placed back onto one of the bunnies of the attacking player.

Red Timid Bunny: The player with this bunny in the Bunny Circle may re-roll any action that involves dice.  This means that any dice that are rolled may be rerolled once (in any order), but the player must use the second roll.</description></topic><topic type="run"><title>Feed All Your Bunnies</title><description>Feed All Your Bunnies may be given to any opponent whose bunnies must each feed the amounts shown on the card by the end of his next turn or die (discarded). Any bunnies that arrive in The Bunny Circle between the time that the card was played and the end of the player’s turn do not have to feed.</description></topic><topic type="run"><title>Everyone Feed A Bunny</title><description>Everyone Feed A Bunny may be given to all opponents with a bunny in The Bunny Circle. Each opponent must feed any one bunny the amounts shown on the card by the end of their next turns or their bunny dies (discarded).

When this card is played, each opponent that has at least one bunny must feed. If an opponent has more than one bunny, then the opponent may choose which bunny to feed. Any bunnies that arrive in The Bunny Circle between the time that the card was played and the end of the player’s turn do not have to feed. If a player has the Red Congenial Bunny, Holographic Bunny or a bunny with The Heavenly Halo, then he may choose one of these bunnies since none of them need to feed.</description></topic><topic type="roaming"><title>Cruise Missile Prime</title><description>Since it is a Roaming Red Run card, Cruise Missile Prime may be placed on any bunny in The Bunny Circle and roams the board clockwise. Players roll the Red 12-sided die as Cruise Missile Prime visits any one of their bunnies in The Bunny Circle. The first player to roll a Prime Number on the Red 12-sided die detonates the missile. The Prime Numbers are: 2, 3, 5, 7, and 11. If any player does not roll a Prime Number on the Red 12-sided die, then the missile moves to the next viable bunny target for the next round of play.

If any player does roll a Prime Number on the Red 12-sided die, then the target bunny must roll higher than 9 on the Black 12-sided die to survive and adjacent bunnies to the target bunny in The Bunny Circle must roll higher than 8 on the Black 12-sided die to survive. Once detonated, the missile is discarded.

If Cruise Missile Prime has no viable bunny targets left in The Bunny Circle, then it is discarded. If Cruise Missile Prime is confined to an area of The Bunny Circle by two or more Barriers and cannot reach a viable bunny target on the other side, then it is removed (discarded). Just like all Roaming Red Run cards, if Cruise Missile Prime hits a Barrier, it will reverse direction and may affect the same player’s bunnies on two consecutive turns.</description></topic><topic type="run"><title>Quite Irascible Diffractable Cheese Balls</title><description>Quite Irascible Diffractable Cheese Balls may be placed on any bunny in The Bunny Circle which must roll 12 on the Black 12-sided die to survive. Bunnies two spaces away from the target bunny in The Bunny Circle must roll higher than 9 on the Black 12-sided die to survive. Bunnies four spaces away from the target bunny in The Bunny Circle must roll higher than 7 on the Black 12-sided die to survive.

Even though every other bunny is initially skipped, wrap around damage may cause a bunny to be hit in the other direction. If a bunny is two spaces to the left of the target bunny and four spaces to the right of the target bunny, then it will be hit twice!</description></topic><topic type="run"><title>Activate The Minilith</title><description>Activate The Minilith may be used once by a player to steal the Minilith from any opponent (saved or in his five-card hand) or to force the opponent with the Minilith saved to roll the seven 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow, Blue, Black and Red). Each Even number rolled forces the opponent to return a Carrot to Kaballa’s Market (even if the market is closed) or to discard a bunny of his choice. Seven Even numbers force all players to return all of their Carrots to Kaballa’s Market and to discard all of their bunnies.</description></topic><topic type="run"><title>Bankruptcy</title><description>Bankruptcy may be given to any player who immediately loses all of his Dolla. The player also loses any Dolla Vouchers that he may have been saving.</description></topic><topic type="run"><title>Barrier</title><description>Barrier may be placed between any two players and stops weapons that affect adjacent bunnies. For example, the effects of a Nuclear Warhead may not reach your bunny if there is a Barrier between it and the target bunny in The Bunny Circle.

Barrier reverses the direction of Roaming Red Run cards (such as Cyber Bunny or Cruise Missile Prime). Barrier will cause any Roaming Run card to move in the opposite direction after it is reversed. Barrier does not stop any multi-target, non-Roaming Red Run card circumstances. More than one Barrier may be placed side by side between the same two players.</description></topic><topic type="run"><title>Carrot Exchange</title><description>Carrot Exchange may be used once by a player to force any opponent to exchange two of his Carrots for one of yours. In order to use this card against an opponent, that player must have at least two Carrots. Carrot Exchange cannot be used for a one to one exchange. The player chooses all three Carrots in the exchange.</description></topic><topic type="run"><title>Clumsy Congenial</title><description>Clumsy Congenial may be placed on any Congenial Bunny in The Bunny Circle which, while opening a package of Melba Toast, flings two sharp pieces in opposite directions instantly killing the two adjacent bunnies. The original target Congenial Bunny is not harmed.</description></topic><topic type="run"><title>Dude, Where’s My Carrot?</title><description>When a player uses Dude, Where’s My Carrot? all of the large Carrot cards held by the players, as well as those still at Kaballa’s Market, are turned face down (as quickly as those still at Kaballa’s Market, are turned face down (as quickly as possible). The Red 12-sided die is rolled and if the player can say who owns the Carrot with the same number, then he will take the Carrot from the opponent or Kaballa’s Market. A wrong guess forces the player to return one of his Carrots to Kaballa’s Market (even if the market is closed). Therefore, it is necessary for a player to have a Carrot to play this card.

Notice that the capital letter T appears in the last die box. This is for the Clear 20-sided die (Violet Booster Deck). Once you have this die in play, a player may use Dude, Where’s My Carrot? twice and try for two Carrots.

If a player does not have one (or two) Carrots to chance, then he may wish to force an opponent to attempt the Dude, Where’s My Carrot? challenge. The opponent must already have one (or two) Carrots to risk because a wrong guess by the opponent will mean that he will lose one (or two) of his Carrots.</description></topic><topic type="run"><title>Holographic Bunny</title><description>Holographic Bunny is a Red Bunny that does not need to feed and cannot be used to win the game since it is not technically alive. This bunny can only be harmed by the Laser Gun, Nuclear Warhead, Miniature Black Hole, Quite Irascible Diffractable Cheese Balls, Bittersweet Chocolate Covered Anti-Matter Raisins (Violet Booster Deck), Plutonium (Orange Booster Deck), Psychic Waves (Twilight White Booster Deck) and Sharks WFLB (Stainless Steel Booster Deck).

The Holographic Bunny may be transformed into a live bunny by using the Ancient Star Rod (Violet Booster Deck). </description></topic><topic type="run"><title>The Mystery Urn</title><description>The player holding The Mystery Urn rolls the Violet 12-sided die. The next player clockwise must roll higher than the highest roll (so far) or that player must donate either a bunny from The Bunny Circle or a saved Carrot to the kitty. The kitty is simply a pile of bunnies and Carrots collected during The Mystery Urn activity.

Play continues clockwise. Each player who has at least one bunny in The Bunny Circle or one saved Carrot must play. The first player to roll a 12 wins the kitty. However, the player who started The Mystery Urn activity will get a final chance to roll a 12 and win the kitty.

If a player gives up his last bunny or Carrot, then he is finished with The Mystery Urn activity and cannot win the kitty.

If all players have lost all of their bunnies and Carrots, then no player wins. All of the bunnies are discarded, and all of the Carrots are returned to Kaballa’s Market (even if the market is closed).

If the initial roll by the player is a 12, then The Mystery Urn activity is over and no one wins anything.

Later, players may feed the kitty with Zodiac cards (Green Booster Deck) and Mysterious Place cards (Ominous Onyx Booster Deck).</description></topic><topic type="special"><title>Rainbo</title><description>Rainbo may be given to any player who must roll the eight 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow, Blue, Black, Red and Pink – Perfectly Pink Booster Deck). All bunnies in The Bunny Circle that are the same color (or half color) as the lowest die rolled are killed immediately. If Black is the lowest die rolled, then all bunnies in The Bunny Circle must die (discarded) regardless of their color or kind (including Specialty bunnies and Celebrity bunnies – Violet and Ominous Onyx Booster Decks). Players (or groups of players) that are isolated by a Barrier on both sides are protected.

Rainbo cannot kill a bunny with The Heavenly Halo or the Holographic Bunny.</description></topic><topic type="special"><title>Red Light District</title><description>Red Light District may be used once by a player to purchase a Red item from any opponent for 5 Dolla: a Red bunny in The Bunny Circle, a Red Pawn (Orange Booster Deck) or a saved Fire symbol Zodiac card (Green Booster Deck). The opponent is given the 5 Dolla.</description></topic><topic type="special"><title>Bounty Mounty</title><description>Bounty Mounty may be placed on any bunny in The Bunny Circle along with a Dolla donation (as bounty). All players may donate Dolla to the bounty. The player who kills the bunny gets the money (Dolla).</description></topic><topic type="special"><title>Free Defense</title><description>Free Defense may be used once by a player to take two Defense Cards from Rooney’s Weapons Emporium. Free Defense may not be used if Rooney’s Weapons Emporium is closed.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>H.E.M.P. (Highly Explosive Missile Package)</title><description>H.E.M.P. may be used once by a player to attack any abducting aliens. The player rolls the Yellow 12-sided die.

9-12 = The aliens and abducted bunnies are destroyed. In addition, the wreckage lands on the player whose bunny (or bunnies) was abducted by the aliens killing all of his other bunnies in The Bunny Circle as well.

5-8 = Only the aliens and abducted bunnies are destroyed.

1-4 = The missile is a dud. Nothing happens!</description></topic><topic type="special"><title>Half Price Coupon Rooney’s Weapons Emporium</title><description>Half Price Coupon may be used for one turn by a player to purchase any items at Rooney’s Weapons Emporium for half price. If the total price of an item or items requires a Half Dolla and no Half Dolla is available (Stainless Steel Booster Deck), then the player must round up to the nearest Dolla.</description></topic><topic type="veryspecial"><title>Bunny To The Future</title><description>Bunny To The Future allows a bunny to avoid the outcome of any weapon by traveling three rounds of play into the future. The bunny is placed off to the side and returns to the player at the start of his third turn after it left The Bunny Circle. If the game ends before the bunny returns, then the bunny is lost. May be used at any time!</description></topic><topic type="veryspecial"><title>Guardian Angle</title><description>Guardian Angle may be used once by a player to eliminate any Terrible Misfortune including Very and Extremely Terrible Misfortune (Ominous Onyx Booster Deck). May be used at any time!</description></topic><topic type="immediate"><title>Zep Tepi</title><description>Zep Tepi must be used once by (or given to) any First Time player who may take any saved Special or Very Special card from each adjacent player.

If the player who picked the card is not a First Time player, then he must give the card to the first First Time player counter-clockwise from him. If no one is a First Time player, then the player who drew the card may use it himself.</description></topic></topics></deck>
