<deck><topics><topic type="cardtype"><title>Specialty Bunnies</title><description>Specialty bunnies have no color (Blue, Green, Orange, Violet or Yellow) or kind (Congenial, Gleeful, Lumbering, Sinister or Timid). Specialty bunnies are their own kind of bunny. A player may, of course, win the game with one of these bunnies in The Bunny Circle.

Specialty bunnies come as singles, doubles or triplets that make forming a Bunny Triplet easier. If a player has three single Specialty bunnies in The Bunny Circle, then he has formed a Bunny Triplet and may play two cards per turn. If a player has a single Specialty Bunny and a double Specialty Bunny, then he has also formed a Bunny Triplet and may play two cards per turn. If a player has a triplet Specialty Bunny in The Bunny Circle, then he automatically has a Bunny Triplet and may play two cards per turn.

If an opponent attacks and kills a Specialty Bunny, then all bunnies in the double or triplet are lost and the card is discarded. In that respect, Specialty Bunny doubles and triplets are treated as a single target. When counting for Roaming Red Run cards, and weapons that affect bunnies many spaces away, Specialty Bunny cards (singles, doubles or triplets) count as one space.</description></topic><topic type="weapon"><title>Earthquake</title><description>Earthquake may be placed on any bunny in The Bunny Circle which must roll higher than 10 on the Black 12-sided die to survive. Adjacent bunnies to the target bunny in The Bunny Circle must roll higher than 9 on the Black 12-sided die to survive.</description></topic><topic type="weapon"><title>Bittersweet Chocolate Covered Anti-Matter Raisins</title><description>Bittersweet Chocolate Covered Anti-Matter Raisins may be placed on any bunny in The Bunny Circle which dies immediately. All bunnies within four spaces of the target bunny in The Bunny Circle are also killed. Clover bunnies (bunnies with Clover cards underneath them) may survive since Clovers lower the level of an attacking weapon.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Bunny Booster</title><description>Bunny Booster may be placed under any bunny and changes its color to Red. Bunnies that become Red will inherit the special feature for that type of bunny. Bunny Booster may be placed under single color (or half color – Green Booster Deck) Congenial, Gleeful, Lumbering, Sinister and Timid bunnies (but not Super bunnies).</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Bunny Exchange</title><description>Bunny Exchange may be used once by a player to force any opponent to exchange two of his bunnies for one of yours. In order to use this card against an opponent, that player must have at least two bunnies. Bunny Exchange cannot be used for a one to one exchange. The player chooses all three bunnies in the exchange. A bunny with The Heavenly Halo may be taken with the Bunny Exchange card.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Low Jack Kojak</title><description>Low Jack Kojak may be used once by a player to take the Carrot with the same number rolled on the Clear 20-sided die from either Kaballa’s Market (even if the market is closed) or an opponent. If any player owned the Carrot, then he must return all of his other Carrots to Kaballa’s Market (even if the market is closed).</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Share The Wealth</title><description>Share The Wealth may be used once by a player with no Dolla to take half of the Dolla from the opponent with the most Dolla. If two opponents have an equal amount of Dolla, then the player may choose which opponent must Share The Wealth. If the opponent with the most Dolla has an odd amount that cannot be divided equally, then he will keep the extra Dolla for himself.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Blown Trojan</title><description>Blown Trojan may be used once by a player to either force The Trojan Bunny in The Bunny Circle to explode immediately or to revive one bunny from the Discard Pile for every two of his bunnies in The Bunny Circle of the same color.

For example, a player with two Orange bunnies in The Bunny Circle may revive any one bunny from the Discard Pile (and immediately place it down next to his other bunnies in The Bunny Circle). A player with three Green bunnies in The Bunny Circle may not pair up the middle one twice to revive two bunnies. However, a player with four Blue bunnies in The Bunny Circle may revive two bunnies from the Discard Pile. Remember that Specialty bunnies and Celebrity bunnies (Ominous Onyx Booster Deck) have no color and cannot be used to revive bunnies with Blown Trojan.

A player may revive any bunny from the Discard Pile (including Free Agent, Holographic, and Specialty) regardless of the color of the bunnies used to revive it.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Bunny Hop</title><description>Bunny Hop may be used once by a player to force any two adjacent players (including himself) to exchange their Bottom and Top Run cards. The Bottom and Top Run cards of the first player become the Bottom and Top Run cards of the second player and vice versa.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Cool Change</title><description>Cool Change may be used once by a player to replace all or some of his seven cards with new cards from the Draw Pile. These may include the Bottom and Top Run cards.</description></topic><topic type="special"><title>Diverse Portfolio</title><description>Diverse Portfolio allows a player to eliminate the Triple Or Trouble (Stainless Steel Booster Deck) after a bad die roll or to counteract the Bankruptcy before losing all of his Dolla. This card must be a saved Special to be used immediately. Remember, to save a Special card, a player must run it through the Bottom and Top Run card cycle. Unlike Very Special cards, Diverse Portfolio may not be used to save other players from financial loss. This card is for the exclusive use of the player who has it saved.</description></topic><topic type="special"><title>La Hot Peppers</title><description>LA Hot Peppers may be used once by a player to double the amount of Water Units needed on any pending Feed The Bunny card on any bunny in The Bunny Circle. The LA stands for Louisiana.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Random Paintball Assault</title><description>Random Paintball Assault may be placed under any bunny or Pawn which becomes the same color as the highest die rolled. If Random Paintball Assault is placed under a bunny and the Black 12-sided die is the highest die rolled, then the bunny dies. Bunnies that become Red or Pink (Perfectly Pink Booster Deck) will inherit the special feature for that type of Red or Pink bunny. Random Paintball Assault may not be placed under Specialty bunnies or Celebrity bunnies (Ominous Onyx Booster Deck).</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Run Amok</title><description>Run Amok may be used once by a player to force any opponent to discard his Bottom and Top Run cards and to replace them with new cards. The opponent may take new cards from the Draw Pile before replacing his Bottom and Top Run cards.</description></topic><topic type="veryspecial"><title>Ancient Star Rod</title><description>Ancient Star Rod may be used once by a player to defend against any weapon. The player rolls the three 12-sided dice (Violet, Blue and Red) and counts the number of Odd rolls.

3 Odd rolls = The weapon is redirected to another bunny in The Bunny Circle.

2 Odd rolls = The weapon is eliminated (discarded).

1 Odd roll = Lame rod. The weapon hits the target bunny normally. Nothing changes!

No Odd rolls = Disaster! The weapon hits the original target bunny with double strength and double range. Double strength doubles the level of the weapon but does not change the die needed to defend against the weapon. Sometimes a weapon that has double strength cannot be defeated. If the weapon is a single target weapon, then double range means that it will affect adjacent bunnies in The Bunny Circle as well. May be used at any time!

If the current date (day, month and year) consists of three Odd numbers, then the player may automatically redirect the weapon without having to roll the dice. If the current date (day, month and year) consists of no Odd numbers, then the Ancient Star Rod may not be used to defend against a weapon at all.

Placing this card under the Holographic Bunny turns it into a live bunny, capable of winning the game, but vulnerable to weapons, Feed The Bunny cards or dangerous circumstances. This action may be performed after the last Carrot has been taken from Kaballa’s Market but before the Magic Carrot is revealed.</description></topic><topic type="veryspecial"><title>Bunnies In Black</title><description>Bunnies In Black protects any one player’s bunnies from alien abductions by the Beyea Aliens or their Mothership (Orange Booster Deck) for the duration of the game providing that this card is a saved Very Special.

Or Bunnies In Black may be used once by a player to retrieve bunnies safely from the Beyea Aliens. Bunnies retrieved become the property of the player and must immediately be placed in The Bunny Circle. A player must discard the Bunnies In Black card after retrieving bunnies from the Beyea Aliens. May be used at any time!</description></topic><topic type="run"><title>Dude, Where’s My Carrot?</title><description>When a player uses Dude, Where’s My Carrot? all of the large Carrot cards held by the players, as well as those still at Kaballa’s Market, are turned face down (as quickly as possible). The Red 12-sided die is rolled and if the player can say who owns the Carrot with the same number, then he will take the Carrot from the opponent or Kaballa’s Market. A wrong guess forces the player to return one of his Carrots to Kaballa’s Market (even if the market is closed). Therefore, it is necessary for a player to have a Carrot to play this card.

The player may then roll the 20-sided die to try a second time, following the same rules.

The player may instead force an opponent to attempt the Dude, Where’s My Carrot? challenge. The opponent must already have one (or two) Carrots to risk because a wrong guess by the opponent will mean that he will lose one (or two) of his Carrots.</description></topic><topic type="run"><title>Holographic Bunny</title><description>Holographic Bunny is a Red Bunny that does not need to feed and cannot be used to win the game since it is not technically alive. This bunny can only be harmed by the Laser Gun, Nuclear Warhead, Miniature Black Hole, Quite Irascible Diffractable Cheese Balls, Bittersweet Chocolate Covered Anti-Matter Raisins, Plutonium (Orange Booster Deck), Psychic Waves (Twilight White Booster Deck) and Sharks WFLB (Stainless Steel Booster Deck).

The Holographic Bunny may be transformed into a live bunny by using the Ancient Star Rod. If the Holographic Bunny should become alive, it will be vulnerable to all weapons and Feed The Bunny cards, and may be used to win the game. Regardless of whether the bunny is Holographic or it becomes alive by using the Ancient Star Rod, it is still a Red bunny and can be used to form a Bunny Triplet with other Red bunnies.</description></topic></topics></deck>
