<deck><topics><topic type="cardtype"><title>50/50 Weapons</title><description>When a player places a 50/50 Weapon on an opponent’s bunny in The Bunny Circle, the opponent must guess which of two dice he will roll higher. If the opponent guesses correctly, then his bunny will survive. If the opponent guesses incorrectly, then his bunny will die (discarded). If the same number appears on both dice, then the opponent must roll both dice again.

50/50 Weapons may not be purchased from Rooney’s Weapons Emporium for any price. Also, players cannot use Defense Cards to eliminate 50/50 Weapons. Weapon Booster or Weapon Reducer (Stainless Steel Booster Deck) cannot be used to change a 50/50 Weapon</description></topic><topic type="gamplay"><title>White Pawn</title><description>The White Pawn may be purchased from Weil’s Pawn Shop and declared any single color. The player must make this decision right away, and the color is not allowed to change during game play. If the White Pawn is returned to Weil’s Pawn Shop during play (perhaps during a Pawn Recall), then the next person to purchase the Pawn may declare it a different color.

When a player owns the White Pawn, it is now possible for him to have two Pawns of the same color. For example, if a player owns the Orange Pawn and the White Pawn (which he has declared Orange), then he may re-roll the Orange 12-sided die twice, use Orange P-Cards (such as the Magic Fountain) two additional times, and need only one Orange bunny in The Bunny Circle to form a Bunny Triplet.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Psychic Waves</title><description>Before playing Psychic Waves on any opponent’s bunny in The Bunny Circle, the player must secretly write down one of the six Symbols (Triangle, Rectangle, Spiral, Ellipse, Star or Cross) on a piece of paper hidden from all of the other players.

The opponent whose bunny was targeted by Psychic Waves will try to guess the Symbol chosen by the player. If the opponent guesses the incorrect Symbol, then his bunny dies. Clover bunnies (bunnies with Clover cards underneath them) may survive since Clovers lower the level of an attacking weapon.

Psychic Waves is then placed on the next bunny clockwise in The Bunny Circle and the process is repeated. This continues up to five times, or until the correct Symbol is guessed. Obviously as Psychic Waves continues, it becomes easier to guess the Symbol with fewer choices.

Psychic Waves is played during one player’s turn, and no Barrier can stop Psychic Waves.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Mob Hit</title><description>Mob Hit may be placed on any bunny in The Bunny Circle which must roll higher than the Dolla amount collected on the Black 12-sided die to survive.

To use this weapon, a player places Mob Hit on any opponent’s bunny. The other players are then asked to donate Dolla to increase the weapon level. The final weapon level is equal to the amount of Dolla donated by all of the players.

Although the opponent is asked to roll the Black 12-sided die to defend against Mob Hit, the weapon level does not have to stop at 12 and may reach any level with generous donations of Dolla. The opponent may save his bunny by using Defense Cards that are equal to the weapon level reached by the other players’ donations. After the weapon has been used, the Dolla is given to Kaballa (discarded). Mob Hit may not be purchased from Rooney’s Weapons Emporium for any price.

If both players in a two-player game have bunnies, then all bunnies squish each other and are killed (discarded). If only one player in a two-player game has bunnies, then all of his bunnies will go to the other player.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Calcite Conundrum</title><description>Calcite Conundrum allows a player to start and maintain a second set of Bottom and Top Run cards using cards from his five-card hand. The player lays down a second Bottom and Top Run card right next to his first. The player’s bunnies in The Bunny Circle are used to play both sets of Bottom and Top Run cards. As play continues (either clockwise or counter-clockwise) the player plays the Top Run card of his first set of cards (and the Bottom Run if he has a Bunny Triplet), finishes using his first set of cards, and then moves on to his second set of cards. After playing the second set of cards, the player’s turn is over. This player will keep four cards down and three cards in his hand at all times.

If at any time the player has no bunnies in The Bunny Circle, then all cards are immediately replaced with cards from the Draw Pile and normal play begins again for that player with seven new cards.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Carousel</title><description>To use Carousel, all players who have reached their 30th birthday must roll the Green and Red 12-sided dice. If a player’s Red 12-sided die roll is higher than his Green 12-sided die roll, then one of his bunnies dies. The player may choose which bunny to sacrifice. If the player has no bunnies in The Bunny Circle, then he must discard all of his Mysterious Place cards (Ominous Onyx Booster Deck). If a player has no bunnies in The Bunny Circle, no Mysterious Place cards or rolled higher on the Green die, then he loses nothing.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Cloning</title><description>Cloning may be used once by a player to clone any of his single color bunnies that are in The Bunny Circle. A player cannot clone Free Agent, Specialty, Double Free Agent, Half Color, Super (Stainless Steal Booster Deck), or Celebrity (Ominous Onyx Booster Deck) bunnies. The same player must own both of the bunnies (the original and the clone) and keep them adjacent to each other in The Bunny Circle. The Cloning card is used to denote the cloned bunny. If the original bunny is abducted, moved, traded or killed, then the clone will die. If the original bunny changes color (perhaps due to a Random Paintball Assault), then the clone will change color as well. The original bunny and the clone do not share Bunny Modifiers. If the clone is given The Heavenly Halo, then it can survive independently of the original bunny.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Heavenly Halo Handoff</title><description>Heavenly Halo Handoff may be used once by a player to remove The Heavenly Halo from any bunny in The Bunny Circle and place it under another bunny the same number of spaces away in The Bunny Circle as rolled on the Yellow 12-sided die. The Heavenly Halo moves clockwise in the AM or counter-clockwise in the PM in The Bunny Circle. If The Heavenly Halo returns to the original bunny from which it was taken, then the player who owns that bunny may choose a Carrot from Kaballa’s Market (if the market is open).</description></topic><topic type="roaming"><title>O.R.P. (Obnoxious Roaming Pest)</title><description>O.R.P. may be given to any player and roams the board counter-clockwise. Since O.R.P. is a Roaming Red Run card, it visits one player (per round) who must roll the seven 12-sided dice (Violet, Orange, Green, Yellow, Blue, Black and Red) and the Clear 20-sided die. The die with the lowest number is the supply that the player loses in its entirety. If two dice are tied for the lowest roll, then the player will lose both supplies. The O.R.P. will skip any player who has at least one saved Zodiac card.

Use the legend below (or the balloons on the card) to determine which supply corresponds to which color:

Violet = Return all bunnies to the Discard Pile near Weil’s Pawn Shop.

Orange = Return all Carrots to Kaballa’s Market (even if the market is closed).

Green = Place all Cabbage Cards in the Discard Pile.

Yellow = Place all Dolla in the Discard Pile.

Blue = Place all Water Cards in the Discard Pile.

Black = Place all Defense Cards in the Discard Pile.

Red = Return all Pawns to Weil’s Pawn Shop.

Clear = The player loses no supply and the O.R.P. dies (discarded).

For example, if a player’s lowest roll is on the Green 12-sided die, then he will lose all of his saved Cabbage Units including any Vouchers. If a player’s lowest roll is on the Red 12-sided die, then he will have to return all of his Pawns to Weil’s Pawn Shop.</description></topic><topic type=""><title> Random Rotational Roaming</title><description>Random Rotational Roaming may be placed on any bunny in The Bunny Circle, saved Zodiac card or saved Mysterious Place card (Ominous Onyx Booster Deck) and moves (clockwise on an Even numbered day or counter-clockwise on an Odd numbered day) to the player the same number of positions away as rolled on the Clear 20-sided die.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Return A Carrot</title><description>Return A Carrot may be used once by a player to force any opponent to return any one of his Carrots to Kaballa’s Market (even if the market is closed). The opponent may choose which of his Carrots to return.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Shockwave</title><description>Shockwave may be placed between any two players. Shockwave pushes all of the bunnies of the two players (one player on each side of the card) to the next adjacent player away from the Shockwave. This occurs on both sides of the card. Bunnies pushed against a Barrier are squished (discarded). Pushed bunnies are positioned in the same order relative to each other for the new player as they were before the Shockwave.

If both players in a two-player game have bunnies, then all bunnies squish each other and are killed (discarded). If only one player in a two-player game has bunnies, then all of his bunnies will go to the other player.</description></topic><topic type=""><title>Signs Of Portent</title><description>Signs Of Portent may be used once by a player to view cards from the top of the small Zodiac Card deck down to the zodiac sign rolled. When a player uses Signs Of Portent, he must first roll the 12-sided Zodiac die. Next, he must flip over cards from the small Zodiac Card deck starting from the top and working his way down to the card that matches the zodiac sign rolled. All players are allowed to see the revealed Zodiac Cards.</description></topic><topic type="special"><title> Forever Fed</title><description>The player with this card saved has no need to feed. Forever Fed keeps all of a single player’s bunnies from needing Cabbage or Water for any reason. If at any time the player has no bunnies in The Bunny Circle, then Forever Fed is discarded immediately. Players cannot save this Special without a bunny in The Bunny Circle.</description></topic><topic type="special"><title> Free Weapon</title><description>Free Weapon may be used once by a player to take any weapon from Rooney’s Weapons Emporium with the same level (or lower) as the number rolled on the Clear 20-sided die. The weapon must be used immediately! Free Weapon may not be used if Rooney’s Weapons Emporium is closed.</description></topic><topic type="special"><title>Gift Certificate Rooney’s Weapons Emporium</title><description>This Gift Certificate may be used only at Rooney’s Weapons Emporium (if the emporium is open). The Dolla amount is determined by the roll of the Black 12-sided die and must be spent immediately.</description></topic><topic type="special"><title>The Golden Ratio (Almost)</title><description>The Golden Ratio may be used once by two players (one with eight Carrots and one with five Carrots). Each player may choose a Carrot from Kaballa’s Market (if the market is open), and take a saved Zodiac card from any opponent. If either player owns the Yellow Pawn, then the rewards are doubled, therefore players may choose two Carrots from Kaballa’s Market and take two saved Zodiac cards from any opponent or opponents.</description></topic><topic type="veryspecial"><title>Blue Angels</title><description>Blue Angels may be used once by a player to eliminate the Sea Whiz Mount, Clumsy Congenial, Anti-Missile, Boomerang, Flying Fritters (Stainless Steal Booster Deck), Vampire Bats (Perfectly Pink Booster Deck) or Bunny Dearest (Ominous Onyx Booster Deck). May be used at any time and kept for the entire game if the player owns the Blue Pawn. If that is the case, then after Blue Angels is played it is simply saved off to the side with a player’s other saved Special (or Very Special) cards and used again when needed. If the player loses or trades the Blue Pawn, then he may use Blue Angels one more time before discarding it.</description></topic><topic type="veryspecial"><title>Defense Card Suspender</title><description>Defense Card Suspender may be used once by a player to suspend the use of all Defense Cards for one round of play. May be used at any time!

For example, let’s pretend that a fictional player Carol wants to land a big weapon on an opponent’s bunny, but she knows that the opponent has Defense Cards. First, Carol would play the Defense Card Suspender so that her opponent cannot use his Defense Cards. Second, Carol would launch the weapon. No player will be allowed to use a Defense Card until Carol’s next turn (after one full round of play has gone by).</description></topic><topic type="veryspecial"><title>Weapon Booster</title><description>Weapon Booster may be used once by a player to boost the weapon level of any weapon placed on any bunny in The Bunny Circle by the amount rolled on the Black 12-sided die. All weapon ranges remain unchanged. May be used at any time!

For example, let’s say that a fictional player Carol uses Sea Whiz Mount (Weapon Level 10) on an opponent’s bunny. She plays Weapon Booster immediately (since Weapon Booster is a Very Special), and rolls a 1 on the Black 12-sided die. The target bunny must now roll higher than 11 to survive, and the adjacent bunnies must roll higher than 10 to survive. The weapon increases its level (from 10 to 11), but does not increase its range.

Defense Cards are used to eliminate the effects of a weapon (for a single player) based solely on the original weapon level. A player with 10 Defense Units could protect his bunnies against Sea Whiz Mount used in our example even if Weapon Booster changed the weapon level to 11.

If Weapon Booster raises the weapon level beyond the maximum roll of the die (and the bunny has no Clovers), then it may be impossible for a player to roll a high enough number to survive.</description></topic><topic type="veryspecial"><title>The White Stuff</title><description>The player with this card saved has exclusive use of the White 12-sided die which may be rolled and substituted for the roll of any other 12-sided die (except the Zodiac die) any time during play. For example, suppose that the player with The White Stuff has a bunny in The Bunny Circle that is given a Random FTB. The player rolls the Green, Blue and White 12-sided dice. The value on the White 12-sided die may be substituted for either the roll of the Green 12-sided die or the roll of the Blue 12-sided die.

The White Stuff may only be used once per any card consequence. In the example before, the White 12-sided die could not have been rolled separately for both the Green and the Blue 12-sided dice. Also, neither the Red Timid Bunny nor the White Pawn will allow a re-roll of the White die.</description></topic><topic type="run"><title>Holographic Bunny</title><description>Holographic Bunny is a Red Bunny that does not need to feed and cannot be used to win the game since it is not technically alive. This bunny can only be harmed by the Laser Gun, Nuclear Warhead, Miniature Black Hole, Quite Irascible Diffractable Cheese Balls, Bittersweet Chocolate Covered Anti-Matter Raisins, Plutonium, Psychic Waves and Sharks WFLB (Stainless Steel Booster Deck).

The Holographic Bunny may be transformed into a live bunny by using the Ancient Star Rod. If the Holographic Bunny should become alive, it will be vulnerable to all weapons and Feed The Bunny cards, and may be used to win the game. Regardless of whether the bunny is Holographic or it becomes alive by using the Ancient Star Rod, it is still a Red bunny and can be used to form a Bunny Triplet with other Red bunnies.</description></topic></topics></deck>
